Game Results:

TOKEN	TAG	GUESS
QUERIES
-------------
Lancashire	ORG	LOC	0
162-4	O	O	0
(	O	O	0
N.	PER	PER	0
Fairbrother	PER	PER	0
53	O	O	0
not	O	O	0
out	O	O	0
)	O	O	0
.	O	O	0

Game History:

-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
Lancashire	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.962,ORG=0.026,O=0.007]	ORG	LOC
162-4	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.001,O=0.997]	O	O
(	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=0.999]	O	O
N.	[PER=0.901,LOC=0.012,ORG=0.015,O=0.072]	PER	PER
Fairbrother	[PER=0.972,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.004,O=0.019]	PER	PER
53	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=0.994]	O	O
not	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
out	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=0.999]	O	O
)	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 0
Current in-flight queries: 
-----------
Move choice:
io.hybridcrowd.gameplay.Game$TurnIn@0
