Game Results:

TOKEN	TAG	GUESS
QUERIES
-------------
Fairview	LOC	LOC	0
,	O	O	0
Texas	LOC	LOC	0
,	O	O	0
$	O	O	0
1.82	O	O	0
million	O	O	0
deal	O	O	0
Baa1	O	O	0
-	O	O	0
Moody	ORG	PER	0
's	ORG	O	0
.	O	O	0

Game History:

-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
Fairview	[PER=0.224,LOC=0.469,ORG=0.241,O=0.066]	LOC	LOC
,	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.025,ORG=0.001,O=0.974]	O	O
Texas	[PER=0.075,LOC=0.892,ORG=0.009,O=0.024]	LOC	LOC
,	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.007,ORG=0.000,O=0.993]	O	O
$	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.000,O=0.999]	O	O
1.82	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
million	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
deal	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.002,O=0.997]	O	O
Baa1	[PER=0.046,LOC=0.062,ORG=0.056,O=0.836]	O	O
-	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=0.998]	O	O
Moody	[PER=0.562,LOC=0.128,ORG=0.050,O=0.260]	ORG	PER
's	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.002,O=0.991]	ORG	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=0.999]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 0
Current in-flight queries: 
-----------
Move choice:
io.hybridcrowd.gameplay.Game$TurnIn@0
