Game Results:

TOKEN	TAG	GUESS
QUERIES
-------------
In	O	O	0
Vaduz	LOC	LOC	0
:	O	O	0
Vaduz	LOC	LOC	0
(	O	O	0
Liechtenstein	LOC	LOC	0
)	O	O	0
1	O	O	0
RAF	ORG	LOC	0
Riga	ORG	LOC	0
(	O	O	0
Latvia	LOC	LOC	0
)	O	O	0
1	O	O	0
(	O	O	0
0-0	O	O	0
)	O	O	0
Scorers	O	O	0
:	O	O	0
Vaduz	LOC	O	0
-	O	O	0
Daniele	PER	PER	0
Polverino	PER	PER	0
(	O	O	0
90th	O	O	0
)	O	O	0
RAF	ORG	LOC	0
Riga	ORG	LOC	0
-	O	O	0
Agrins	PER	PER	0
Zarins	PER	PER	0
(	O	O	0
47th	O	O	0
)	O	O	0
Aggregate	O	O	0
2-2	O	O	0
.	O	O	0

Game History:

-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
In	[PER=0.082,LOC=0.023,ORG=0.104,O=0.791]	O	O
Vaduz	[PER=0.399,LOC=0.452,ORG=0.115,O=0.034]	LOC	LOC
:	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.992]	O	O
Vaduz	[PER=0.389,LOC=0.519,ORG=0.051,O=0.041]	LOC	LOC
(	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.002,ORG=0.000,O=0.994]	O	O
Liechtenstein	[PER=0.186,LOC=0.691,ORG=0.098,O=0.026]	LOC	LOC
)	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.000,O=0.999]	O	O
1	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.000,O=0.999]	O	O
RAF	[PER=0.050,LOC=0.732,ORG=0.184,O=0.034]	ORG	LOC
Riga	[PER=0.043,LOC=0.813,ORG=0.139,O=0.006]	ORG	LOC
(	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.000,O=0.995]	O	O
Latvia	[PER=0.007,LOC=0.979,ORG=0.008,O=0.006]	LOC	LOC
)	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.000,O=0.999]	O	O
1	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
(	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
0-0	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=0.999]	O	O
)	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
Scorers	[PER=0.031,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.007,O=0.959]	O	O
:	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=0.999]	O	O
Vaduz	[PER=0.296,LOC=0.286,ORG=0.051,O=0.367]	LOC	O
-	[PER=0.046,LOC=0.002,ORG=0.016,O=0.937]	O	O
Daniele	[PER=0.639,LOC=0.022,ORG=0.325,O=0.013]	PER	PER
Polverino	[PER=0.644,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.305,O=0.034]	PER	PER
(	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=0.999]	O	O
90th	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=0.999]	O	O
)	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.000,O=0.999]	O	O
RAF	[PER=0.051,LOC=0.731,ORG=0.184,O=0.034]	ORG	LOC
Riga	[PER=0.045,LOC=0.811,ORG=0.139,O=0.006]	ORG	LOC
-	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.997]	O	O
Agrins	[PER=0.848,LOC=0.041,ORG=0.038,O=0.072]	PER	PER
Zarins	[PER=0.849,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.025,O=0.122]	PER	PER
(	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=0.999]	O	O
47th	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=0.999]	O	O
)	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
Aggregate	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.005,O=0.975]	O	O
2-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.000,O=0.999]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 0
Current in-flight queries: 
-----------
Move choice:
io.hybridcrowd.gameplay.Game$TurnIn@0
