Game Results:

TOKEN	TAG	GUESS
QUERIES
-------------
Constructorol	ORG	O	0
-	O	O	0
Sergei	PER	PER	0
Rogachev	PER	PER	0
(	O	O	0
42nd	O	O	0
)	O	O	0
,	O	O	0
Gennadi	PER	PER	0
Skidan	PER	PER	0
(	O	O	0
87th	O	O	0
)	O	O	0
.	O	O	0

Game History:

-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
Constructorol	[PER=0.030,LOC=0.031,ORG=0.090,O=0.850]	ORG	O
-	[PER=0.008,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.003,O=0.989]	O	O
Sergei	[PER=0.957,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.026,O=0.001]	PER	PER
Rogachev	[PER=0.938,LOC=0.017,ORG=0.039,O=0.007]	PER	PER
(	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=0.999]	O	O
42nd	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.003,O=0.990]	O	O
)	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
,	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=0.999]	O	O
Gennadi	[PER=0.950,LOC=0.017,ORG=0.029,O=0.004]	PER	PER
Skidan	[PER=0.917,LOC=0.020,ORG=0.052,O=0.011]	PER	PER
(	[PER=0.007,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.991]	O	O
87th	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=0.999]	O	O
)	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 0
Current in-flight queries: 
-----------
Move choice:
io.hybridcrowd.gameplay.Game$TurnIn@0
