Game Results:

TOKEN	TAG	GUESS
QUERIES
-------------
Northamptonshire	ORG	LOC	0
160-4	O	O	0
(	O	O	0
K.	PER	PER	0
Curran	PER	PER	0
79	O	O	0
not	O	O	0
out	O	O	0
)	O	O	0
.	O	O	0

Game History:

-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
Northamptonshire	[PER=0.009,LOC=0.954,ORG=0.030,O=0.006]	ORG	LOC
160-4	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.001,O=0.997]	O	O
(	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=0.999]	O	O
K.	[PER=0.940,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.021,O=0.036]	PER	PER
Curran	[PER=0.961,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.019,O=0.015]	PER	PER
79	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=0.994]	O	O
not	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
out	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=0.999]	O	O
)	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 0
Current in-flight queries: 
-----------
Move choice:
io.hybridcrowd.gameplay.Game$TurnIn@0
