Game Results:

TOKEN	TAG	GUESS
QUERIES
-------------
SOCCER	O	O	0
-	O	O	0
KEANE	PER	LOC	0
SIGNS	O	LOC	0
FOUR-YEAR	O	LOC	0
CONTRACT	O	O	0
WITH	O	O	0
MANCHESTER	LOC	LOC	0
UNITED	LOC	LOC	0
.	O	O	0

Game History:

-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
SOCCER	[PER=0.010,LOC=0.088,ORG=0.060,O=0.842]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.002,O=0.997]	O	O
KEANE	[PER=0.073,LOC=0.349,ORG=0.442,O=0.136]	PER	LOC
SIGNS	[PER=0.037,LOC=0.363,ORG=0.451,O=0.149]	O	LOC
FOUR-YEAR	[PER=0.018,LOC=0.531,ORG=0.415,O=0.035]	O	LOC
CONTRACT	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.174,ORG=0.246,O=0.574]	O	O
WITH	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.039,ORG=0.043,O=0.917]	O	O
MANCHESTER	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.897,ORG=0.088,O=0.010]	LOC	LOC
UNITED	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.851,ORG=0.091,O=0.054]	LOC	LOC
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 0
Current in-flight queries: 
-----------
Move choice:
io.hybridcrowd.gameplay.Game$TurnIn@0
