Game Results:

TOKEN	TAG	GUESS
QUERIES
-------------
Arafat	PER	PER	0
to	O	O	0
meet	O	O	0
Peres	PER	PER	0
in	O	O	0
Gaza	LOC	LOC	0
after	O	O	0
flight	O	O	0
ban	O	O	0
.	O	O	0

Game History:

-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
Arafat	[PER=0.397,LOC=0.102,ORG=0.140,O=0.360]	PER	PER
to	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.002,O=0.996]	O	O
meet	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
Peres	[PER=0.552,LOC=0.328,ORG=0.091,O=0.029]	PER	PER
in	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.006,O=0.986]	O	O
Gaza	[PER=0.080,LOC=0.874,ORG=0.022,O=0.024]	LOC	LOC
after	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
flight	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=0.999]	O	O
ban	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 0
Current in-flight queries: 
-----------
Move choice:
io.hybridcrowd.gameplay.Game$TurnIn@0
