Game Results:

TOKEN	TAG	GUESS
QUERIES
-------------
CRICKET	O	O	4
-	O	O	1
ENGLAND	LOC	LOC	4
100-2	O	O	3
AT	O	O	4
LUNCH	O	O	4
ON	O	O	3
FIRST	O	O	4
DAY	O	O	4
OF	O	O	2
THIRD	O	O	3
TEST	O	O	2
.	O	O	0

Game History:

-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.045,LOC=0.376,ORG=0.383,O=0.196]	O	LOC
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.016,O=0.983]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.026,LOC=0.398,ORG=0.334,O=0.241]	LOC	ORG
100-2	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.013,ORG=0.285,O=0.697]	O	ORG
AT	[PER=0.013,LOC=0.065,ORG=0.688,O=0.234]	O	ORG
LUNCH	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.069,ORG=0.718,O=0.200]	O	ORG
ON	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.040,ORG=0.697,O=0.259]	O	ORG
FIRST	[PER=0.008,LOC=0.056,ORG=0.860,O=0.075]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.021,LOC=0.112,ORG=0.719,O=0.149]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.404,O=0.589]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.160,ORG=0.334,O=0.489]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.043,ORG=0.169,O=0.785]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 0
Current in-flight queries: 
-----------
Move choice:
Making job posting
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.045,LOC=0.376,ORG=0.383,O=0.196]	O	LOC
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.016,O=0.983]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.026,LOC=0.398,ORG=0.334,O=0.241]	LOC	ORG
100-2	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.013,ORG=0.285,O=0.697]	O	ORG
AT	[PER=0.013,LOC=0.065,ORG=0.688,O=0.234]	O	ORG
LUNCH	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.069,ORG=0.718,O=0.200]	O	ORG
ON	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.040,ORG=0.697,O=0.259]	O	ORG
FIRST	[PER=0.008,LOC=0.056,ORG=0.860,O=0.075]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.021,LOC=0.112,ORG=0.719,O=0.149]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.404,O=0.589]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.160,ORG=0.334,O=0.489]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.043,ORG=0.169,O=0.785]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 1
Current available humans: 0
Current in-flight queries: 
-----------
Next event:
io.hybridcrowd.gameplay.Game$HumanArrival@90
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.045,LOC=0.376,ORG=0.383,O=0.196]	O	LOC
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.016,O=0.983]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.026,LOC=0.398,ORG=0.334,O=0.241]	LOC	ORG
100-2	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.013,ORG=0.285,O=0.697]	O	ORG
AT	[PER=0.013,LOC=0.065,ORG=0.688,O=0.234]	O	ORG
LUNCH	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.069,ORG=0.718,O=0.200]	O	ORG
ON	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.040,ORG=0.697,O=0.259]	O	ORG
FIRST	[PER=0.008,LOC=0.056,ORG=0.860,O=0.075]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.021,LOC=0.112,ORG=0.719,O=0.149]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.404,O=0.589]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.160,ORG=0.334,O=0.489]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.043,ORG=0.169,O=0.785]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 1
Current in-flight queries: 
-----------
Move choice:
Making job posting
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.045,LOC=0.376,ORG=0.383,O=0.196]	O	LOC
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.016,O=0.983]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.026,LOC=0.398,ORG=0.334,O=0.241]	LOC	ORG
100-2	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.013,ORG=0.285,O=0.697]	O	ORG
AT	[PER=0.013,LOC=0.065,ORG=0.688,O=0.234]	O	ORG
LUNCH	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.069,ORG=0.718,O=0.200]	O	ORG
ON	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.040,ORG=0.697,O=0.259]	O	ORG
FIRST	[PER=0.008,LOC=0.056,ORG=0.860,O=0.075]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.021,LOC=0.112,ORG=0.719,O=0.149]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.404,O=0.589]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.160,ORG=0.334,O=0.489]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.043,ORG=0.169,O=0.785]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 1
Current available humans: 1
Current in-flight queries: 
-----------
Next event:
io.hybridcrowd.gameplay.Game$HumanArrival@a9
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.045,LOC=0.376,ORG=0.383,O=0.196]	O	LOC
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.016,O=0.983]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.026,LOC=0.398,ORG=0.334,O=0.241]	LOC	ORG
100-2	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.013,ORG=0.285,O=0.697]	O	ORG
AT	[PER=0.013,LOC=0.065,ORG=0.688,O=0.234]	O	ORG
LUNCH	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.069,ORG=0.718,O=0.200]	O	ORG
ON	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.040,ORG=0.697,O=0.259]	O	ORG
FIRST	[PER=0.008,LOC=0.056,ORG=0.860,O=0.075]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.021,LOC=0.112,ORG=0.719,O=0.149]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.404,O=0.589]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.160,ORG=0.334,O=0.489]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.043,ORG=0.169,O=0.785]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 2
Current in-flight queries: 
-----------
Move choice:
Making job posting
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.045,LOC=0.376,ORG=0.383,O=0.196]	O	LOC
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.016,O=0.983]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.026,LOC=0.398,ORG=0.334,O=0.241]	LOC	ORG
100-2	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.013,ORG=0.285,O=0.697]	O	ORG
AT	[PER=0.013,LOC=0.065,ORG=0.688,O=0.234]	O	ORG
LUNCH	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.069,ORG=0.718,O=0.200]	O	ORG
ON	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.040,ORG=0.697,O=0.259]	O	ORG
FIRST	[PER=0.008,LOC=0.056,ORG=0.860,O=0.075]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.021,LOC=0.112,ORG=0.719,O=0.149]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.404,O=0.589]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.160,ORG=0.334,O=0.489]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.043,ORG=0.169,O=0.785]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 1
Current available humans: 2
Current in-flight queries: 
-----------
Next event:
io.hybridcrowd.gameplay.Game$HumanArrival@a9
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.045,LOC=0.376,ORG=0.383,O=0.196]	O	LOC
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.016,O=0.983]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.026,LOC=0.398,ORG=0.334,O=0.241]	LOC	ORG
100-2	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.013,ORG=0.285,O=0.697]	O	ORG
AT	[PER=0.013,LOC=0.065,ORG=0.688,O=0.234]	O	ORG
LUNCH	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.069,ORG=0.718,O=0.200]	O	ORG
ON	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.040,ORG=0.697,O=0.259]	O	ORG
FIRST	[PER=0.008,LOC=0.056,ORG=0.860,O=0.075]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.021,LOC=0.112,ORG=0.719,O=0.149]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.404,O=0.589]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.160,ORG=0.334,O=0.489]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.043,ORG=0.169,O=0.785]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
-----------
Move choice:
Making job posting
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.045,LOC=0.376,ORG=0.383,O=0.196]	O	LOC
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.016,O=0.983]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.026,LOC=0.398,ORG=0.334,O=0.241]	LOC	ORG
100-2	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.013,ORG=0.285,O=0.697]	O	ORG
AT	[PER=0.013,LOC=0.065,ORG=0.688,O=0.234]	O	ORG
LUNCH	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.069,ORG=0.718,O=0.200]	O	ORG
ON	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.040,ORG=0.697,O=0.259]	O	ORG
FIRST	[PER=0.008,LOC=0.056,ORG=0.860,O=0.075]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.021,LOC=0.112,ORG=0.719,O=0.149]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.404,O=0.589]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.160,ORG=0.334,O=0.489]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.043,ORG=0.169,O=0.785]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 1
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
-----------
Next event:
io.hybridcrowd.gameplay.Game$HumanArrival@c4
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.045,LOC=0.376,ORG=0.383,O=0.196]	O	LOC
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.016,O=0.983]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.026,LOC=0.398,ORG=0.334,O=0.241]	LOC	ORG
100-2	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.013,ORG=0.285,O=0.697]	O	ORG
AT	[PER=0.013,LOC=0.065,ORG=0.688,O=0.234]	O	ORG
LUNCH	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.069,ORG=0.718,O=0.200]	O	ORG
ON	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.040,ORG=0.697,O=0.259]	O	ORG
FIRST	[PER=0.008,LOC=0.056,ORG=0.860,O=0.075]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.021,LOC=0.112,ORG=0.719,O=0.149]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.404,O=0.589]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.160,ORG=0.334,O=0.489]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.043,ORG=0.169,O=0.785]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 0 "CRICKET"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.045,LOC=0.376,ORG=0.383,O=0.196]	O	LOC
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.016,O=0.983]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.026,LOC=0.398,ORG=0.334,O=0.241]	LOC	ORG
100-2	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.013,ORG=0.285,O=0.697]	O	ORG
AT	[PER=0.013,LOC=0.065,ORG=0.688,O=0.234]	O	ORG
LUNCH	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.069,ORG=0.718,O=0.200]	O	ORG
ON	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.040,ORG=0.697,O=0.259]	O	ORG
FIRST	[PER=0.008,LOC=0.056,ORG=0.860,O=0.075]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.021,LOC=0.112,ORG=0.719,O=0.149]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.404,O=0.589]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.160,ORG=0.334,O=0.489]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.043,ORG=0.169,O=0.785]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	CRICKET
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 0 "CRICKET"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.045,LOC=0.376,ORG=0.383,O=0.196]	O	LOC
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.016,O=0.983]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.026,LOC=0.398,ORG=0.334,O=0.241]	LOC	ORG
100-2	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.013,ORG=0.285,O=0.697]	O	ORG
AT	[PER=0.013,LOC=0.065,ORG=0.688,O=0.234]	O	ORG
LUNCH	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.069,ORG=0.718,O=0.200]	O	ORG
ON	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.040,ORG=0.697,O=0.259]	O	ORG
FIRST	[PER=0.008,LOC=0.056,ORG=0.860,O=0.075]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.021,LOC=0.112,ORG=0.719,O=0.149]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.404,O=0.589]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.160,ORG=0.334,O=0.489]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.043,ORG=0.169,O=0.785]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	CRICKET
	CRICKET
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 0 "CRICKET"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.045,LOC=0.376,ORG=0.383,O=0.196]	O	LOC
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.016,O=0.983]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.026,LOC=0.398,ORG=0.334,O=0.241]	LOC	ORG
100-2	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.013,ORG=0.285,O=0.697]	O	ORG
AT	[PER=0.013,LOC=0.065,ORG=0.688,O=0.234]	O	ORG
LUNCH	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.069,ORG=0.718,O=0.200]	O	ORG
ON	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.040,ORG=0.697,O=0.259]	O	ORG
FIRST	[PER=0.008,LOC=0.056,ORG=0.860,O=0.075]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.021,LOC=0.112,ORG=0.719,O=0.149]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.404,O=0.589]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.160,ORG=0.334,O=0.489]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.043,ORG=0.169,O=0.785]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	CRICKET
	CRICKET
	CRICKET
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 0 "CRICKET"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.045,LOC=0.376,ORG=0.383,O=0.196]	O	LOC
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.016,O=0.983]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.026,LOC=0.398,ORG=0.334,O=0.241]	LOC	ORG
100-2	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.013,ORG=0.285,O=0.697]	O	ORG
AT	[PER=0.013,LOC=0.065,ORG=0.688,O=0.234]	O	ORG
LUNCH	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.069,ORG=0.718,O=0.200]	O	ORG
ON	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.040,ORG=0.697,O=0.259]	O	ORG
FIRST	[PER=0.008,LOC=0.056,ORG=0.860,O=0.075]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.021,LOC=0.112,ORG=0.719,O=0.149]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.404,O=0.589]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.160,ORG=0.334,O=0.489]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.043,ORG=0.169,O=0.785]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	CRICKET
	CRICKET
	CRICKET
	CRICKET
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 1 "-"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.045,LOC=0.376,ORG=0.383,O=0.196]	O	LOC
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.016,O=0.983]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.026,LOC=0.398,ORG=0.334,O=0.241]	LOC	ORG
100-2	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.013,ORG=0.285,O=0.697]	O	ORG
AT	[PER=0.013,LOC=0.065,ORG=0.688,O=0.234]	O	ORG
LUNCH	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.069,ORG=0.718,O=0.200]	O	ORG
ON	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.040,ORG=0.697,O=0.259]	O	ORG
FIRST	[PER=0.008,LOC=0.056,ORG=0.860,O=0.075]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.021,LOC=0.112,ORG=0.719,O=0.149]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.404,O=0.589]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.160,ORG=0.334,O=0.489]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.043,ORG=0.169,O=0.785]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	CRICKET
	CRICKET
	CRICKET
	CRICKET
	-
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 0 "CRICKET" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.021,LOC=0.173,ORG=0.176,O=0.631]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.008,O=0.992]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.026,LOC=0.401,ORG=0.329,O=0.243]	LOC	ORG
100-2	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.013,ORG=0.281,O=0.701]	O	ORG
AT	[PER=0.013,LOC=0.065,ORG=0.686,O=0.235]	O	ORG
LUNCH	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.070,ORG=0.717,O=0.201]	O	ORG
ON	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.040,ORG=0.696,O=0.260]	O	ORG
FIRST	[PER=0.008,LOC=0.057,ORG=0.860,O=0.076]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.021,LOC=0.112,ORG=0.718,O=0.149]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.404,O=0.590]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.160,ORG=0.334,O=0.490]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.043,ORG=0.169,O=0.785]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	CRICKET
	CRICKET
	CRICKET
	-
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 2 "ENGLAND"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.021,LOC=0.173,ORG=0.176,O=0.631]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.008,O=0.992]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.026,LOC=0.401,ORG=0.329,O=0.243]	LOC	ORG
100-2	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.013,ORG=0.281,O=0.701]	O	ORG
AT	[PER=0.013,LOC=0.065,ORG=0.686,O=0.235]	O	ORG
LUNCH	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.070,ORG=0.717,O=0.201]	O	ORG
ON	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.040,ORG=0.696,O=0.260]	O	ORG
FIRST	[PER=0.008,LOC=0.057,ORG=0.860,O=0.076]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.021,LOC=0.112,ORG=0.718,O=0.149]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.404,O=0.590]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.160,ORG=0.334,O=0.490]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.043,ORG=0.169,O=0.785]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	CRICKET
	CRICKET
	CRICKET
	ENGLAND
	-
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 0 "CRICKET" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.036,ORG=0.037,O=0.923]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.002,O=0.998]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.026,LOC=0.403,ORG=0.326,O=0.245]	LOC	ORG
100-2	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.013,ORG=0.278,O=0.703]	O	ORG
AT	[PER=0.013,LOC=0.065,ORG=0.685,O=0.236]	O	ORG
LUNCH	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.070,ORG=0.716,O=0.202]	O	ORG
ON	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.040,ORG=0.695,O=0.261]	O	ORG
FIRST	[PER=0.008,LOC=0.057,ORG=0.860,O=0.076]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.021,LOC=0.112,ORG=0.718,O=0.149]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.404,O=0.590]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.160,ORG=0.334,O=0.490]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.043,ORG=0.169,O=0.785]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	CRICKET
	CRICKET
	ENGLAND
	-
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 0 "CRICKET" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.006,O=0.988]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.999]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.026,LOC=0.404,ORG=0.325,O=0.245]	LOC	ORG
100-2	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.013,ORG=0.278,O=0.704]	O	ORG
AT	[PER=0.013,LOC=0.065,ORG=0.685,O=0.237]	O	ORG
LUNCH	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.070,ORG=0.716,O=0.202]	O	ORG
ON	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.040,ORG=0.695,O=0.261]	O	ORG
FIRST	[PER=0.008,LOC=0.057,ORG=0.859,O=0.076]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.021,LOC=0.112,ORG=0.718,O=0.149]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.404,O=0.590]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.160,ORG=0.334,O=0.490]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.043,ORG=0.169,O=0.785]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	CRICKET
	ENGLAND
	-
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 0 "CRICKET" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=0.999]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.026,LOC=0.404,ORG=0.325,O=0.245]	LOC	ORG
100-2	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.013,ORG=0.278,O=0.704]	O	ORG
AT	[PER=0.013,LOC=0.065,ORG=0.685,O=0.237]	O	ORG
LUNCH	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.070,ORG=0.716,O=0.202]	O	ORG
ON	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.040,ORG=0.695,O=0.261]	O	ORG
FIRST	[PER=0.008,LOC=0.057,ORG=0.859,O=0.076]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.021,LOC=0.112,ORG=0.718,O=0.149]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.404,O=0.590]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.160,ORG=0.334,O=0.490]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.043,ORG=0.169,O=0.785]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	ENGLAND
	-
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 1 "-" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.026,LOC=0.404,ORG=0.325,O=0.245]	LOC	ORG
100-2	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.013,ORG=0.277,O=0.704]	O	ORG
AT	[PER=0.013,LOC=0.065,ORG=0.685,O=0.237]	O	ORG
LUNCH	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.070,ORG=0.716,O=0.202]	O	ORG
ON	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.040,ORG=0.695,O=0.261]	O	ORG
FIRST	[PER=0.008,LOC=0.057,ORG=0.859,O=0.076]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.021,LOC=0.112,ORG=0.718,O=0.149]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.404,O=0.590]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.160,ORG=0.334,O=0.490]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.043,ORG=0.169,O=0.785]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	ENGLAND
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 2 "ENGLAND"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.026,LOC=0.404,ORG=0.325,O=0.245]	LOC	ORG
100-2	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.013,ORG=0.277,O=0.704]	O	ORG
AT	[PER=0.013,LOC=0.065,ORG=0.685,O=0.237]	O	ORG
LUNCH	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.070,ORG=0.716,O=0.202]	O	ORG
ON	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.040,ORG=0.695,O=0.261]	O	ORG
FIRST	[PER=0.008,LOC=0.057,ORG=0.859,O=0.076]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.021,LOC=0.112,ORG=0.718,O=0.149]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.404,O=0.590]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.160,ORG=0.334,O=0.490]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.043,ORG=0.169,O=0.785]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	ENGLAND
	ENGLAND
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 2 "ENGLAND"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.026,LOC=0.404,ORG=0.325,O=0.245]	LOC	ORG
100-2	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.013,ORG=0.277,O=0.704]	O	ORG
AT	[PER=0.013,LOC=0.065,ORG=0.685,O=0.237]	O	ORG
LUNCH	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.070,ORG=0.716,O=0.202]	O	ORG
ON	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.040,ORG=0.695,O=0.261]	O	ORG
FIRST	[PER=0.008,LOC=0.057,ORG=0.859,O=0.076]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.021,LOC=0.112,ORG=0.718,O=0.149]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.404,O=0.590]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.160,ORG=0.334,O=0.490]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.043,ORG=0.169,O=0.785]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	ENGLAND
	ENGLAND
	ENGLAND
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 2 "ENGLAND"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.026,LOC=0.404,ORG=0.325,O=0.245]	LOC	ORG
100-2	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.013,ORG=0.277,O=0.704]	O	ORG
AT	[PER=0.013,LOC=0.065,ORG=0.685,O=0.237]	O	ORG
LUNCH	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.070,ORG=0.716,O=0.202]	O	ORG
ON	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.040,ORG=0.695,O=0.261]	O	ORG
FIRST	[PER=0.008,LOC=0.057,ORG=0.859,O=0.076]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.021,LOC=0.112,ORG=0.718,O=0.149]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.404,O=0.590]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.160,ORG=0.334,O=0.490]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.043,ORG=0.169,O=0.785]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	ENGLAND
	ENGLAND
	ENGLAND
	ENGLAND
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 3 "100-2"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.026,LOC=0.404,ORG=0.325,O=0.245]	LOC	ORG
100-2	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.013,ORG=0.277,O=0.704]	O	ORG
AT	[PER=0.013,LOC=0.065,ORG=0.685,O=0.237]	O	ORG
LUNCH	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.070,ORG=0.716,O=0.202]	O	ORG
ON	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.040,ORG=0.695,O=0.261]	O	ORG
FIRST	[PER=0.008,LOC=0.057,ORG=0.859,O=0.076]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.021,LOC=0.112,ORG=0.718,O=0.149]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.404,O=0.590]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.160,ORG=0.334,O=0.490]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.043,ORG=0.169,O=0.785]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	ENGLAND
	ENGLAND
	ENGLAND
	100-2
	ENGLAND
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 2 "ENGLAND" = LOC
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.008,LOC=0.826,ORG=0.095,O=0.072]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.023,ORG=0.099,O=0.875]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.083,ORG=0.607,O=0.294]	O	ORG
LUNCH	[PER=0.014,LOC=0.085,ORG=0.656,O=0.245]	O	ORG
ON	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.047,ORG=0.645,O=0.304]	O	ORG
FIRST	[PER=0.009,LOC=0.065,ORG=0.838,O=0.088]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.022,LOC=0.119,ORG=0.701,O=0.158]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.395,O=0.599]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.161,ORG=0.327,O=0.495]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.043,ORG=0.165,O=0.788]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	ENGLAND
	ENGLAND
	100-2
	ENGLAND
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 2 "ENGLAND" = ORG
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.526,ORG=0.423,O=0.046]	LOC	ORG
100-2	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.351,O=0.631]	O	ORG
AT	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.060,ORG=0.715,O=0.213]	O	ORG
LUNCH	[PER=0.011,LOC=0.065,ORG=0.739,O=0.185]	O	ORG
ON	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.038,ORG=0.714,O=0.245]	O	ORG
FIRST	[PER=0.007,LOC=0.054,ORG=0.868,O=0.071]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.021,LOC=0.109,ORG=0.724,O=0.146]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.407,O=0.586]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.160,ORG=0.337,O=0.488]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.043,ORG=0.170,O=0.784]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	ENGLAND
	100-2
	ENGLAND
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 3 "100-2"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.526,ORG=0.423,O=0.046]	LOC	ORG
100-2	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.351,O=0.631]	O	ORG
AT	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.060,ORG=0.715,O=0.213]	O	ORG
LUNCH	[PER=0.011,LOC=0.065,ORG=0.739,O=0.185]	O	ORG
ON	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.038,ORG=0.714,O=0.245]	O	ORG
FIRST	[PER=0.007,LOC=0.054,ORG=0.868,O=0.071]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.021,LOC=0.109,ORG=0.724,O=0.146]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.407,O=0.586]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.160,ORG=0.337,O=0.488]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.043,ORG=0.170,O=0.784]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	ENGLAND
	100-2
	100-2
	ENGLAND
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 2 "ENGLAND" = LOC
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.886,ORG=0.102,O=0.011]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.025,ORG=0.103,O=0.870]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.083,ORG=0.609,O=0.293]	O	ORG
LUNCH	[PER=0.014,LOC=0.085,ORG=0.657,O=0.244]	O	ORG
ON	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.047,ORG=0.646,O=0.303]	O	ORG
FIRST	[PER=0.009,LOC=0.065,ORG=0.838,O=0.087]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.022,LOC=0.119,ORG=0.701,O=0.158]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.395,O=0.599]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.161,ORG=0.327,O=0.495]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.043,ORG=0.165,O=0.788]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	ENGLAND
	100-2
	100-2
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 3 "100-2"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.886,ORG=0.102,O=0.011]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.025,ORG=0.103,O=0.870]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.083,ORG=0.609,O=0.293]	O	ORG
LUNCH	[PER=0.014,LOC=0.085,ORG=0.657,O=0.244]	O	ORG
ON	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.047,ORG=0.646,O=0.303]	O	ORG
FIRST	[PER=0.009,LOC=0.065,ORG=0.838,O=0.087]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.022,LOC=0.119,ORG=0.701,O=0.158]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.395,O=0.599]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.161,ORG=0.327,O=0.495]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.043,ORG=0.165,O=0.788]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	ENGLAND
	100-2
	100-2
	100-2
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 4 "AT"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.886,ORG=0.102,O=0.011]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.025,ORG=0.103,O=0.870]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.083,ORG=0.609,O=0.293]	O	ORG
LUNCH	[PER=0.014,LOC=0.085,ORG=0.657,O=0.244]	O	ORG
ON	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.047,ORG=0.646,O=0.303]	O	ORG
FIRST	[PER=0.009,LOC=0.065,ORG=0.838,O=0.087]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.022,LOC=0.119,ORG=0.701,O=0.158]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.395,O=0.599]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.161,ORG=0.327,O=0.495]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.043,ORG=0.165,O=0.788]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	ENGLAND
	100-2
	100-2
	100-2
	AT
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 2 "ENGLAND" = LOC
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.982,ORG=0.016,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.027,ORG=0.037,O=0.933]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.090,ORG=0.581,O=0.314]	O	ORG
LUNCH	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.091,ORG=0.635,O=0.260]	O	ORG
ON	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.049,ORG=0.628,O=0.318]	O	ORG
FIRST	[PER=0.009,LOC=0.068,ORG=0.831,O=0.092]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.022,LOC=0.122,ORG=0.695,O=0.161]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.391,O=0.602]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.162,ORG=0.325,O=0.497]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.043,ORG=0.164,O=0.789]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	100-2
	100-2
	100-2
	AT
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 3 "100-2" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.993,ORG=0.005,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.006,O=0.990]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.084,ORG=0.573,O=0.327]	O	ORG
LUNCH	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.089,ORG=0.630,O=0.266]	O	ORG
ON	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.049,ORG=0.624,O=0.322]	O	ORG
FIRST	[PER=0.009,LOC=0.069,ORG=0.829,O=0.093]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.022,LOC=0.122,ORG=0.694,O=0.162]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.391,O=0.603]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.162,ORG=0.324,O=0.498]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.043,ORG=0.164,O=0.790]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	100-2
	100-2
	AT
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 4 "AT"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.993,ORG=0.005,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.006,O=0.990]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.084,ORG=0.573,O=0.327]	O	ORG
LUNCH	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.089,ORG=0.630,O=0.266]	O	ORG
ON	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.049,ORG=0.624,O=0.322]	O	ORG
FIRST	[PER=0.009,LOC=0.069,ORG=0.829,O=0.093]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.022,LOC=0.122,ORG=0.694,O=0.162]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.391,O=0.603]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.162,ORG=0.324,O=0.498]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.043,ORG=0.164,O=0.790]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	100-2
	AT
	100-2
	AT
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 3 "100-2" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.994,ORG=0.004,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.999]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.084,ORG=0.572,O=0.328]	O	ORG
LUNCH	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.089,ORG=0.629,O=0.267]	O	ORG
ON	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.049,ORG=0.624,O=0.323]	O	ORG
FIRST	[PER=0.009,LOC=0.069,ORG=0.829,O=0.093]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.022,LOC=0.122,ORG=0.694,O=0.162]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.391,O=0.603]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.162,ORG=0.324,O=0.498]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.043,ORG=0.164,O=0.790]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	100-2
	AT
	AT
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 3 "100-2" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.995,ORG=0.004,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.083,ORG=0.572,O=0.329]	O	ORG
LUNCH	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.089,ORG=0.629,O=0.267]	O	ORG
ON	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.049,ORG=0.623,O=0.323]	O	ORG
FIRST	[PER=0.009,LOC=0.069,ORG=0.829,O=0.093]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.022,LOC=0.122,ORG=0.694,O=0.162]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.391,O=0.603]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.162,ORG=0.324,O=0.498]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.043,ORG=0.164,O=0.790]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	AT
	AT
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 4 "AT"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.995,ORG=0.004,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.083,ORG=0.572,O=0.329]	O	ORG
LUNCH	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.089,ORG=0.629,O=0.267]	O	ORG
ON	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.049,ORG=0.623,O=0.323]	O	ORG
FIRST	[PER=0.009,LOC=0.069,ORG=0.829,O=0.093]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.022,LOC=0.122,ORG=0.694,O=0.162]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.391,O=0.603]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.162,ORG=0.324,O=0.498]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.043,ORG=0.164,O=0.790]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	AT
	AT
	AT
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 4 "AT"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.995,ORG=0.004,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.083,ORG=0.572,O=0.329]	O	ORG
LUNCH	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.089,ORG=0.629,O=0.267]	O	ORG
ON	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.049,ORG=0.623,O=0.323]	O	ORG
FIRST	[PER=0.009,LOC=0.069,ORG=0.829,O=0.093]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.022,LOC=0.122,ORG=0.694,O=0.162]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.391,O=0.603]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.162,ORG=0.324,O=0.498]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.043,ORG=0.164,O=0.790]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	AT
	AT
	AT
	AT
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 5 "LUNCH"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.995,ORG=0.004,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.083,ORG=0.572,O=0.329]	O	ORG
LUNCH	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.089,ORG=0.629,O=0.267]	O	ORG
ON	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.049,ORG=0.623,O=0.323]	O	ORG
FIRST	[PER=0.009,LOC=0.069,ORG=0.829,O=0.093]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.022,LOC=0.122,ORG=0.694,O=0.162]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.391,O=0.603]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.162,ORG=0.324,O=0.498]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.043,ORG=0.164,O=0.790]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	AT
	AT
	LUNCH
	AT
	AT
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 4 "AT" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.995,ORG=0.004,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.028,ORG=0.192,O=0.774]	O	O
LUNCH	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.110,ORG=0.350,O=0.524]	O	O
ON	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.067,ORG=0.394,O=0.533]	O	O
FIRST	[PER=0.014,LOC=0.104,ORG=0.733,O=0.149]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.025,LOC=0.153,ORG=0.619,O=0.203]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.350,O=0.643]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.017,LOC=0.167,ORG=0.294,O=0.522]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.043,ORG=0.149,O=0.804]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.999]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	AT
	AT
	LUNCH
	AT
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 4 "AT" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.995,ORG=0.004,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.034,O=0.960]	O	O
LUNCH	[PER=0.017,LOC=0.119,ORG=0.233,O=0.631]	O	O
ON	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.075,ORG=0.299,O=0.620]	O	O
FIRST	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.119,ORG=0.694,O=0.172]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.026,LOC=0.166,ORG=0.587,O=0.221]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.332,O=0.660]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.017,LOC=0.169,ORG=0.282,O=0.532]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.044,ORG=0.143,O=0.809]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.999]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	AT
	LUNCH
	AT
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 4 "AT" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.995,ORG=0.004,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.005,O=0.994]	O	O
LUNCH	[PER=0.017,LOC=0.120,ORG=0.212,O=0.651]	O	O
ON	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.076,ORG=0.281,O=0.636]	O	O
FIRST	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.121,ORG=0.686,O=0.176]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.027,LOC=0.168,ORG=0.582,O=0.224]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.329,O=0.663]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.017,LOC=0.170,ORG=0.279,O=0.534]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.044,ORG=0.142,O=0.810]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.999]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	AT
	LUNCH
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 5 "LUNCH"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.995,ORG=0.004,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.005,O=0.994]	O	O
LUNCH	[PER=0.017,LOC=0.120,ORG=0.212,O=0.651]	O	O
ON	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.076,ORG=0.281,O=0.636]	O	O
FIRST	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.121,ORG=0.686,O=0.176]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.027,LOC=0.168,ORG=0.582,O=0.224]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.329,O=0.663]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.017,LOC=0.170,ORG=0.279,O=0.534]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.044,ORG=0.142,O=0.810]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.999]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	AT
	LUNCH
	LUNCH
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 5 "LUNCH" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.995,ORG=0.004,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
LUNCH	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.025,ORG=0.043,O=0.929]	O	O
ON	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.061,ORG=0.146,O=0.788]	O	O
FIRST	[PER=0.018,LOC=0.131,ORG=0.639,O=0.212]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.028,LOC=0.180,ORG=0.544,O=0.248]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.309,O=0.684]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.017,LOC=0.172,ORG=0.264,O=0.547]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.044,ORG=0.135,O=0.817]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.999]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	AT
	LUNCH
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 4 "AT" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.995,ORG=0.004,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
LUNCH	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.024,ORG=0.042,O=0.930]	O	O
ON	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.061,ORG=0.146,O=0.789]	O	O
FIRST	[PER=0.018,LOC=0.131,ORG=0.639,O=0.212]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.028,LOC=0.180,ORG=0.544,O=0.248]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.309,O=0.684]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.017,LOC=0.172,ORG=0.264,O=0.547]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.044,ORG=0.135,O=0.817]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.999]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	LUNCH
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 5 "LUNCH"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.995,ORG=0.004,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
LUNCH	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.024,ORG=0.042,O=0.930]	O	O
ON	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.061,ORG=0.146,O=0.789]	O	O
FIRST	[PER=0.018,LOC=0.131,ORG=0.639,O=0.212]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.028,LOC=0.180,ORG=0.544,O=0.248]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.309,O=0.684]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.017,LOC=0.172,ORG=0.264,O=0.547]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.044,ORG=0.135,O=0.817]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.999]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	LUNCH
	LUNCH
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 5 "LUNCH"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.995,ORG=0.004,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
LUNCH	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.024,ORG=0.042,O=0.930]	O	O
ON	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.061,ORG=0.146,O=0.789]	O	O
FIRST	[PER=0.018,LOC=0.131,ORG=0.639,O=0.212]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.028,LOC=0.180,ORG=0.544,O=0.248]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.309,O=0.684]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.017,LOC=0.172,ORG=0.264,O=0.547]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.044,ORG=0.135,O=0.817]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.999]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	LUNCH
	LUNCH
	LUNCH
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 6 "ON"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.995,ORG=0.004,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
LUNCH	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.024,ORG=0.042,O=0.930]	O	O
ON	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.061,ORG=0.146,O=0.789]	O	O
FIRST	[PER=0.018,LOC=0.131,ORG=0.639,O=0.212]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.028,LOC=0.180,ORG=0.544,O=0.248]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.309,O=0.684]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.017,LOC=0.172,ORG=0.264,O=0.547]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.044,ORG=0.135,O=0.817]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.999]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	ON
	LUNCH
	LUNCH
	LUNCH
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 6 "ON"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.995,ORG=0.004,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
LUNCH	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.024,ORG=0.042,O=0.930]	O	O
ON	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.061,ORG=0.146,O=0.789]	O	O
FIRST	[PER=0.018,LOC=0.131,ORG=0.639,O=0.212]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.028,LOC=0.180,ORG=0.544,O=0.248]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.309,O=0.684]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.017,LOC=0.172,ORG=0.264,O=0.547]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.044,ORG=0.135,O=0.817]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.999]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	ON
	LUNCH
	LUNCH
	LUNCH
	ON
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 5 "LUNCH" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.995,ORG=0.004,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
LUNCH	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.006,O=0.989]	O	O
ON	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.057,ORG=0.117,O=0.822]	O	O
FIRST	[PER=0.019,LOC=0.133,ORG=0.628,O=0.220]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.028,LOC=0.182,ORG=0.536,O=0.253]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.304,O=0.688]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.017,LOC=0.173,ORG=0.261,O=0.549]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.044,ORG=0.134,O=0.819]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.999]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	ON
	LUNCH
	LUNCH
	ON
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 5 "LUNCH" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.995,ORG=0.004,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
LUNCH	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
ON	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.057,ORG=0.112,O=0.827]	O	O
FIRST	[PER=0.019,LOC=0.134,ORG=0.627,O=0.221]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.029,LOC=0.183,ORG=0.535,O=0.254]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.304,O=0.689]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.017,LOC=0.173,ORG=0.261,O=0.550]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.044,ORG=0.133,O=0.819]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.999]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	ON
	LUNCH
	ON
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 5 "LUNCH" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.995,ORG=0.004,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
LUNCH	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ON	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.057,ORG=0.112,O=0.827]	O	O
FIRST	[PER=0.019,LOC=0.134,ORG=0.627,O=0.221]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.029,LOC=0.183,ORG=0.535,O=0.254]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.304,O=0.689]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.017,LOC=0.173,ORG=0.260,O=0.550]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.044,ORG=0.133,O=0.819]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.999]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	ON
	ON
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 6 "ON"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.995,ORG=0.004,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
LUNCH	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ON	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.057,ORG=0.112,O=0.827]	O	O
FIRST	[PER=0.019,LOC=0.134,ORG=0.627,O=0.221]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.029,LOC=0.183,ORG=0.535,O=0.254]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.304,O=0.689]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.017,LOC=0.173,ORG=0.260,O=0.550]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.044,ORG=0.133,O=0.819]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.999]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	ON
	ON
	ON
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 7 "FIRST"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.995,ORG=0.004,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
LUNCH	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ON	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.057,ORG=0.112,O=0.827]	O	O
FIRST	[PER=0.019,LOC=0.134,ORG=0.627,O=0.221]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.029,LOC=0.183,ORG=0.535,O=0.254]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.304,O=0.689]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.017,LOC=0.173,ORG=0.260,O=0.550]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.044,ORG=0.133,O=0.819]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.999]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	ON
	FIRST
	ON
	ON
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 6 "ON" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.995,ORG=0.004,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
LUNCH	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ON	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.019,O=0.971]	O	O
FIRST	[PER=0.020,LOC=0.125,ORG=0.605,O=0.250]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.029,LOC=0.182,ORG=0.519,O=0.269]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.295,O=0.697]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.017,LOC=0.174,ORG=0.254,O=0.555]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.044,ORG=0.130,O=0.822]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.999]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	FIRST
	ON
	ON
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 6 "ON" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.995,ORG=0.004,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
LUNCH	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ON	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.003,O=0.996]	O	O
FIRST	[PER=0.020,LOC=0.124,ORG=0.602,O=0.254]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.030,LOC=0.182,ORG=0.516,O=0.272]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.293,O=0.699]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.017,LOC=0.174,ORG=0.253,O=0.556]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.044,ORG=0.130,O=0.823]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.999]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	FIRST
	ON
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 6 "ON" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.995,ORG=0.004,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
LUNCH	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ON	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=0.999]	O	O
FIRST	[PER=0.020,LOC=0.124,ORG=0.601,O=0.255]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.030,LOC=0.182,ORG=0.516,O=0.272]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.293,O=0.699]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.017,LOC=0.174,ORG=0.253,O=0.556]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.044,ORG=0.130,O=0.823]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.999]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	FIRST
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 7 "FIRST"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.995,ORG=0.004,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
LUNCH	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ON	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=0.999]	O	O
FIRST	[PER=0.020,LOC=0.124,ORG=0.601,O=0.255]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.030,LOC=0.182,ORG=0.516,O=0.272]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.293,O=0.699]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.017,LOC=0.174,ORG=0.253,O=0.556]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.044,ORG=0.130,O=0.823]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.999]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	FIRST
	FIRST
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 7 "FIRST"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.995,ORG=0.004,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
LUNCH	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ON	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=0.999]	O	O
FIRST	[PER=0.020,LOC=0.124,ORG=0.601,O=0.255]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.030,LOC=0.182,ORG=0.516,O=0.272]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.293,O=0.699]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.017,LOC=0.174,ORG=0.253,O=0.556]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.044,ORG=0.130,O=0.823]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.999]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	FIRST
	FIRST
	FIRST
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 7 "FIRST"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.995,ORG=0.004,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
LUNCH	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ON	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=0.999]	O	O
FIRST	[PER=0.020,LOC=0.124,ORG=0.601,O=0.255]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.030,LOC=0.182,ORG=0.516,O=0.272]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.293,O=0.699]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.017,LOC=0.174,ORG=0.253,O=0.556]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.044,ORG=0.130,O=0.823]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.999]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	FIRST
	FIRST
	FIRST
	FIRST
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 8 "DAY"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.995,ORG=0.004,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
LUNCH	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ON	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=0.999]	O	O
FIRST	[PER=0.020,LOC=0.124,ORG=0.601,O=0.255]	O	ORG
DAY	[PER=0.030,LOC=0.182,ORG=0.516,O=0.272]	O	ORG
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.293,O=0.699]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.017,LOC=0.174,ORG=0.253,O=0.556]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.044,ORG=0.130,O=0.823]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.999]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	FIRST
	FIRST
	FIRST
	FIRST
	DAY
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 7 "FIRST" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.995,ORG=0.004,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
LUNCH	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ON	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
FIRST	[PER=0.008,LOC=0.049,ORG=0.237,O=0.706]	O	O
DAY	[PER=0.029,LOC=0.207,ORG=0.237,O=0.526]	O	O
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.141,O=0.851]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.017,LOC=0.194,ORG=0.141,O=0.648]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.046,ORG=0.076,O=0.875]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.999]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	FIRST
	FIRST
	FIRST
	DAY
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 8 "DAY"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.995,ORG=0.004,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
LUNCH	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ON	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
FIRST	[PER=0.008,LOC=0.049,ORG=0.237,O=0.706]	O	O
DAY	[PER=0.029,LOC=0.207,ORG=0.237,O=0.526]	O	O
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.141,O=0.851]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.017,LOC=0.194,ORG=0.141,O=0.648]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.046,ORG=0.076,O=0.875]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.999]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	FIRST
	DAY
	FIRST
	FIRST
	DAY
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 7 "FIRST" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.995,ORG=0.004,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
LUNCH	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ON	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
FIRST	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.009,ORG=0.045,O=0.944]	O	O
DAY	[PER=0.029,LOC=0.221,ORG=0.090,O=0.660]	O	O
OF	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.007,ORG=0.060,O=0.932]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.018,LOC=0.204,ORG=0.082,O=0.697]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.047,ORG=0.047,O=0.902]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=0.999]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	DAY
	FIRST
	FIRST
	DAY
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 7 "FIRST" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.995,ORG=0.004,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
LUNCH	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ON	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
FIRST	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.007,O=0.992]	O	O
DAY	[PER=0.029,LOC=0.223,ORG=0.061,O=0.687]	O	O
OF	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.007,ORG=0.044,O=0.948]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.018,LOC=0.206,ORG=0.070,O=0.706]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.047,ORG=0.042,O=0.908]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=0.999]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	DAY
	FIRST
	DAY
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 7 "FIRST" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.995,ORG=0.004,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
LUNCH	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ON	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
FIRST	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.999]	O	O
DAY	[PER=0.029,LOC=0.224,ORG=0.056,O=0.691]	O	O
OF	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.007,ORG=0.042,O=0.950]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.018,LOC=0.206,ORG=0.068,O=0.708]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.047,ORG=0.041,O=0.908]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=0.999]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	DAY
	DAY
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 8 "DAY"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.995,ORG=0.004,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
LUNCH	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ON	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
FIRST	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.999]	O	O
DAY	[PER=0.029,LOC=0.224,ORG=0.056,O=0.691]	O	O
OF	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.007,ORG=0.042,O=0.950]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.018,LOC=0.206,ORG=0.068,O=0.708]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.047,ORG=0.041,O=0.908]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=0.999]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	DAY
	DAY
	DAY
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 8 "DAY"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.995,ORG=0.004,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
LUNCH	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ON	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
FIRST	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.999]	O	O
DAY	[PER=0.029,LOC=0.224,ORG=0.056,O=0.691]	O	O
OF	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.007,ORG=0.042,O=0.950]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.018,LOC=0.206,ORG=0.068,O=0.708]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.047,ORG=0.041,O=0.908]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=0.999]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	DAY
	DAY
	DAY
	DAY
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 9 "OF"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.995,ORG=0.004,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
LUNCH	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ON	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
FIRST	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.999]	O	O
DAY	[PER=0.029,LOC=0.224,ORG=0.056,O=0.691]	O	O
OF	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.007,ORG=0.042,O=0.950]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.018,LOC=0.206,ORG=0.068,O=0.708]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.047,ORG=0.041,O=0.908]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=0.999]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	DAY
	DAY
	DAY
	DAY
	OF
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 8 "DAY" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.995,ORG=0.004,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
LUNCH	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ON	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
FIRST	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
DAY	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.043,ORG=0.011,O=0.940]	O	O
OF	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.017,O=0.979]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.018,LOC=0.208,ORG=0.050,O=0.724]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.047,ORG=0.032,O=0.917]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=0.999]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	DAY
	DAY
	DAY
	OF
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 9 "OF"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.995,ORG=0.004,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
LUNCH	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ON	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
FIRST	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
DAY	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.043,ORG=0.011,O=0.940]	O	O
OF	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.017,O=0.979]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.018,LOC=0.208,ORG=0.050,O=0.724]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.047,ORG=0.032,O=0.917]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=0.999]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	DAY
	DAY
	OF
	DAY
	OF
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 8 "DAY" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.995,ORG=0.004,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
LUNCH	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ON	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
FIRST	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
DAY	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.007,ORG=0.002,O=0.991]	O	O
OF	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.012,O=0.985]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.018,LOC=0.208,ORG=0.046,O=0.728]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.047,ORG=0.030,O=0.919]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=0.999]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	DAY
	OF
	DAY
	OF
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 8 "DAY" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.995,ORG=0.004,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
LUNCH	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ON	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
FIRST	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
DAY	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.000,O=0.999]	O	O
OF	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.011,O=0.985]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.018,LOC=0.208,ORG=0.046,O=0.728]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.047,ORG=0.030,O=0.919]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=0.999]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	OF
	DAY
	OF
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 10 "THIRD"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.995,ORG=0.004,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
LUNCH	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ON	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
FIRST	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
DAY	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.000,O=0.999]	O	O
OF	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.011,O=0.985]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.018,LOC=0.208,ORG=0.046,O=0.728]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.047,ORG=0.030,O=0.919]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=0.999]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	THIRD
	OF
	DAY
	OF
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 8 "DAY" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.995,ORG=0.004,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
LUNCH	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ON	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
FIRST	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
DAY	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
OF	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.011,O=0.986]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.018,LOC=0.208,ORG=0.046,O=0.728]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.048,ORG=0.030,O=0.919]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=0.999]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	THIRD
	OF
	OF
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 9 "OF" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.995,ORG=0.004,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
LUNCH	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ON	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
FIRST	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
DAY	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
OF	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.002,O=0.998]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.017,LOC=0.209,ORG=0.039,O=0.735]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.047,ORG=0.027,O=0.922]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	THIRD
	OF
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 10 "THIRD"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.995,ORG=0.004,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
LUNCH	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ON	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
FIRST	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
DAY	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
OF	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.002,O=0.998]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.017,LOC=0.209,ORG=0.039,O=0.735]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.047,ORG=0.027,O=0.922]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	THIRD
	THIRD
	OF
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 10 "THIRD" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.995,ORG=0.004,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
LUNCH	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ON	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
FIRST	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
DAY	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
OF	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.999]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.039,ORG=0.007,O=0.951]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.027,ORG=0.012,O=0.959]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	THIRD
	OF
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 9 "OF" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.995,ORG=0.004,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
LUNCH	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ON	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
FIRST	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
DAY	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
OF	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.039,ORG=0.007,O=0.951]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.027,ORG=0.012,O=0.959]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	THIRD
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 10 "THIRD"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.995,ORG=0.004,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
LUNCH	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ON	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
FIRST	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
DAY	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
OF	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.039,ORG=0.007,O=0.951]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.027,ORG=0.012,O=0.959]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	THIRD
	THIRD
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 11 "TEST"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.995,ORG=0.004,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
LUNCH	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ON	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
FIRST	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
DAY	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
OF	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.039,ORG=0.007,O=0.951]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.027,ORG=0.012,O=0.959]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	THIRD
	THIRD
	TEST
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 11 "TEST"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.995,ORG=0.004,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
LUNCH	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ON	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
FIRST	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
DAY	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
OF	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.039,ORG=0.007,O=0.951]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.027,ORG=0.012,O=0.959]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	THIRD
	TEST
	THIRD
	TEST
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 11 "TEST" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.995,ORG=0.004,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
LUNCH	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ON	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
FIRST	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
DAY	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
OF	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.035,ORG=0.004,O=0.958]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.002,O=0.994]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	THIRD
	TEST
	THIRD
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 10 "THIRD" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.995,ORG=0.004,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
LUNCH	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ON	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
FIRST	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
DAY	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
OF	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.001,O=0.994]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.001,O=0.995]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	THIRD
	TEST
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 10 "THIRD" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.995,ORG=0.004,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
LUNCH	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ON	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
FIRST	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
DAY	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
OF	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.000,O=0.999]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.001,O=0.995]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	TEST
-----------
Move choice:
io.hybridcrowd.gameplay.Game$Wait@2d1
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.995,ORG=0.004,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
LUNCH	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ON	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
FIRST	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
DAY	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
OF	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.000,O=0.999]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.001,O=0.995]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
	TEST
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 11 "TEST" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
CRICKET	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ENGLAND	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.995,ORG=0.004,O=0.002]	LOC	LOC
100-2	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
AT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
LUNCH	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
ON	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
FIRST	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
DAY	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
OF	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
THIRD	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.000,O=0.999]	O	O
TEST	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=0.999]	O	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
-----------
Move choice:
io.hybridcrowd.gameplay.Game$TurnIn@2ea
