Game Results:

TOKEN	TAG	GUESS
QUERIES
-------------
REUTER	PER	ORG	3
HORSE	O	O	3
RACING	O	O	3
-	O	O	2
PIVOTAL	PER	O	3
ENDS	O	O	3
25-YEAR	O	O	3
WAIT	O	O	3
FOR	O	O	3
TRAINER	O	O	3
PRESCOTT	PER	ORG	3
.	O	O	0

Game History:

-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.011,LOC=0.043,ORG=0.937,O=0.009]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.020,ORG=0.976,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.049,ORG=0.925,O=0.021]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.106,O=0.893]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.956,O=0.020]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.988,O=0.006]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.960,O=0.030]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.987,O=0.002]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.975,O=0.006]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.051,ORG=0.943,O=0.003]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.048,ORG=0.879,O=0.068]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.006,O=0.993]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 0
Current in-flight queries: 
-----------
Move choice:
Making job posting
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.011,LOC=0.043,ORG=0.937,O=0.009]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.020,ORG=0.976,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.049,ORG=0.925,O=0.021]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.106,O=0.893]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.956,O=0.020]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.988,O=0.006]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.960,O=0.030]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.987,O=0.002]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.975,O=0.006]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.051,ORG=0.943,O=0.003]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.048,ORG=0.879,O=0.068]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.006,O=0.993]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 1
Current available humans: 0
Current in-flight queries: 
-----------
Next event:
io.hybridcrowd.gameplay.Game$HumanArrival@0
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.011,LOC=0.043,ORG=0.937,O=0.009]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.020,ORG=0.976,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.049,ORG=0.925,O=0.021]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.106,O=0.893]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.956,O=0.020]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.988,O=0.006]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.960,O=0.030]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.987,O=0.002]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.975,O=0.006]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.051,ORG=0.943,O=0.003]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.048,ORG=0.879,O=0.068]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.006,O=0.993]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 1
Current in-flight queries: 
-----------
Move choice:
Making job posting
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.011,LOC=0.043,ORG=0.937,O=0.009]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.020,ORG=0.976,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.049,ORG=0.925,O=0.021]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.106,O=0.893]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.956,O=0.020]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.988,O=0.006]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.960,O=0.030]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.987,O=0.002]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.975,O=0.006]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.051,ORG=0.943,O=0.003]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.048,ORG=0.879,O=0.068]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.006,O=0.993]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 1
Current available humans: 1
Current in-flight queries: 
-----------
Next event:
io.hybridcrowd.gameplay.Game$HumanArrival@1
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.011,LOC=0.043,ORG=0.937,O=0.009]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.020,ORG=0.976,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.049,ORG=0.925,O=0.021]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.106,O=0.893]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.956,O=0.020]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.988,O=0.006]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.960,O=0.030]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.987,O=0.002]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.975,O=0.006]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.051,ORG=0.943,O=0.003]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.048,ORG=0.879,O=0.068]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.006,O=0.993]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 2
Current in-flight queries: 
-----------
Move choice:
Making job posting
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.011,LOC=0.043,ORG=0.937,O=0.009]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.020,ORG=0.976,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.049,ORG=0.925,O=0.021]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.106,O=0.893]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.956,O=0.020]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.988,O=0.006]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.960,O=0.030]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.987,O=0.002]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.975,O=0.006]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.051,ORG=0.943,O=0.003]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.048,ORG=0.879,O=0.068]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.006,O=0.993]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 1
Current available humans: 2
Current in-flight queries: 
-----------
Next event:
io.hybridcrowd.gameplay.Game$HumanArrival@1
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.011,LOC=0.043,ORG=0.937,O=0.009]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.020,ORG=0.976,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.049,ORG=0.925,O=0.021]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.106,O=0.893]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.956,O=0.020]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.988,O=0.006]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.960,O=0.030]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.987,O=0.002]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.975,O=0.006]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.051,ORG=0.943,O=0.003]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.048,ORG=0.879,O=0.068]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.006,O=0.993]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 0 "REUTER"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.011,LOC=0.043,ORG=0.937,O=0.009]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.020,ORG=0.976,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.049,ORG=0.925,O=0.021]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.106,O=0.893]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.956,O=0.020]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.988,O=0.006]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.960,O=0.030]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.987,O=0.002]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.975,O=0.006]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.051,ORG=0.943,O=0.003]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.048,ORG=0.879,O=0.068]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.006,O=0.993]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	REUTER
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 0 "REUTER"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.011,LOC=0.043,ORG=0.937,O=0.009]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.020,ORG=0.976,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.049,ORG=0.925,O=0.021]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.106,O=0.893]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.956,O=0.020]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.988,O=0.006]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.960,O=0.030]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.987,O=0.002]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.975,O=0.006]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.051,ORG=0.943,O=0.003]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.048,ORG=0.879,O=0.068]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.006,O=0.993]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	REUTER
	REUTER
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 0 "REUTER"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.011,LOC=0.043,ORG=0.937,O=0.009]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.020,ORG=0.976,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.049,ORG=0.925,O=0.021]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.106,O=0.893]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.956,O=0.020]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.988,O=0.006]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.960,O=0.030]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.987,O=0.002]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.975,O=0.006]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.051,ORG=0.943,O=0.003]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.048,ORG=0.879,O=0.068]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.006,O=0.993]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	REUTER
	REUTER
	REUTER
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 1 "HORSE"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.011,LOC=0.043,ORG=0.937,O=0.009]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.020,ORG=0.976,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.049,ORG=0.925,O=0.021]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.106,O=0.893]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.956,O=0.020]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.988,O=0.006]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.960,O=0.030]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.987,O=0.002]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.975,O=0.006]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.051,ORG=0.943,O=0.003]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.048,ORG=0.879,O=0.068]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.006,O=0.993]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	REUTER
	HORSE
	REUTER
	REUTER
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 0 "REUTER" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.010,LOC=0.041,ORG=0.890,O=0.059]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.023,ORG=0.971,O=0.002]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.051,ORG=0.921,O=0.022]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.106,O=0.894]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.956,O=0.020]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.988,O=0.006]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.960,O=0.030]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.987,O=0.002]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.975,O=0.006]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.051,ORG=0.943,O=0.003]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.048,ORG=0.879,O=0.068]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.006,O=0.993]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	HORSE
	REUTER
	REUTER
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 1 "HORSE"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.010,LOC=0.041,ORG=0.890,O=0.059]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.023,ORG=0.971,O=0.002]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.051,ORG=0.921,O=0.022]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.106,O=0.894]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.956,O=0.020]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.988,O=0.006]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.960,O=0.030]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.987,O=0.002]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.975,O=0.006]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.051,ORG=0.943,O=0.003]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.048,ORG=0.879,O=0.068]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.006,O=0.993]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	HORSE
	HORSE
	REUTER
	REUTER
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 0 "REUTER" = ORG
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.007,ORG=0.983,O=0.009]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.993,O=0.000]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.037,ORG=0.940,O=0.018]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.108,O=0.891]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.956,O=0.020]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.988,O=0.006]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.960,O=0.030]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.987,O=0.002]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.975,O=0.006]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.051,ORG=0.943,O=0.003]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.048,ORG=0.879,O=0.068]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.006,O=0.993]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	HORSE
	HORSE
	REUTER
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 1 "HORSE" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.007,ORG=0.981,O=0.010]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.990,O=0.003]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.038,ORG=0.938,O=0.019]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.108,O=0.892]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.956,O=0.020]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.988,O=0.006]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.960,O=0.030]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.987,O=0.002]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.975,O=0.006]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.051,ORG=0.943,O=0.003]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.048,ORG=0.879,O=0.068]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.006,O=0.993]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	HORSE
	REUTER
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 0 "REUTER" = ORG
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.997,O=0.002]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.002,ORG=0.995,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.035,ORG=0.943,O=0.018]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.108,O=0.891]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.956,O=0.020]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.988,O=0.006]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.960,O=0.030]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.987,O=0.002]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.975,O=0.006]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.051,ORG=0.943,O=0.003]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.048,ORG=0.879,O=0.068]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.006,O=0.993]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	HORSE
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 2 "RACING"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.997,O=0.002]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.002,ORG=0.995,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.035,ORG=0.943,O=0.018]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.108,O=0.891]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.956,O=0.020]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.988,O=0.006]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.960,O=0.030]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.987,O=0.002]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.975,O=0.006]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.051,ORG=0.943,O=0.003]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.048,ORG=0.879,O=0.068]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.006,O=0.993]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	RACING
	HORSE
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 2 "RACING"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.997,O=0.002]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.002,ORG=0.995,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.035,ORG=0.943,O=0.018]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.108,O=0.891]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.956,O=0.020]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.988,O=0.006]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.960,O=0.030]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.987,O=0.002]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.975,O=0.006]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.051,ORG=0.943,O=0.003]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.048,ORG=0.879,O=0.068]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.006,O=0.993]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	RACING
	HORSE
	RACING
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 2 "RACING" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.002,ORG=0.996,O=0.002]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.990,O=0.005]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.032,ORG=0.849,O=0.115]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.098,O=0.902]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.955,O=0.020]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.988,O=0.006]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.960,O=0.030]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.987,O=0.002]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.975,O=0.006]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.051,ORG=0.943,O=0.003]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.048,ORG=0.879,O=0.068]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.006,O=0.993]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	HORSE
	RACING
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 1 "HORSE" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.991,O=0.006]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.961,O=0.033]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.033,ORG=0.827,O=0.137]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.095,O=0.904]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.955,O=0.020]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.988,O=0.006]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.960,O=0.030]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.987,O=0.002]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.975,O=0.006]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.051,ORG=0.943,O=0.003]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.048,ORG=0.879,O=0.068]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.006,O=0.993]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	RACING
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 1 "HORSE"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.991,O=0.006]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.961,O=0.033]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.033,ORG=0.827,O=0.137]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.095,O=0.904]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.955,O=0.020]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.988,O=0.006]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.960,O=0.030]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.987,O=0.002]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.975,O=0.006]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.051,ORG=0.943,O=0.003]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.048,ORG=0.879,O=0.068]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.006,O=0.993]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	HORSE
	RACING
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 2 "RACING"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.991,O=0.006]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.961,O=0.033]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.033,ORG=0.827,O=0.137]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.095,O=0.904]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.955,O=0.020]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.988,O=0.006]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.960,O=0.030]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.987,O=0.002]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.975,O=0.006]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.051,ORG=0.943,O=0.003]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.048,ORG=0.879,O=0.068]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.006,O=0.993]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	RACING
	HORSE
	RACING
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 2 "RACING" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.009,ORG=0.973,O=0.017]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.011,ORG=0.873,O=0.114]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.018,ORG=0.454,O=0.526]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.053,O=0.947]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.020,ORG=0.953,O=0.021]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.987,O=0.006]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.959,O=0.030]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.987,O=0.002]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.975,O=0.006]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.051,ORG=0.943,O=0.003]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.048,ORG=0.879,O=0.068]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.006,O=0.993]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	RACING
	HORSE
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 1 "HORSE" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.030,ORG=0.903,O=0.064]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.520,O=0.473]	O	O
RACING	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.273,O=0.709]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.032,O=0.968]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.020,ORG=0.952,O=0.021]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.987,O=0.006]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.959,O=0.030]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.987,O=0.002]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.975,O=0.006]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.051,ORG=0.943,O=0.003]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.048,ORG=0.879,O=0.068]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.006,O=0.993]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	RACING
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 3 "-"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.030,ORG=0.903,O=0.064]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.520,O=0.473]	O	O
RACING	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.273,O=0.709]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.032,O=0.968]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.020,ORG=0.952,O=0.021]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.987,O=0.006]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.959,O=0.030]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.987,O=0.002]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.975,O=0.006]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.051,ORG=0.943,O=0.003]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.048,ORG=0.879,O=0.068]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.006,O=0.993]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	-
	RACING
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 3 "-"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.030,ORG=0.903,O=0.064]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.520,O=0.473]	O	O
RACING	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.273,O=0.709]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.032,O=0.968]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.020,ORG=0.952,O=0.021]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.987,O=0.006]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.959,O=0.030]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.987,O=0.002]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.975,O=0.006]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.051,ORG=0.943,O=0.003]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.048,ORG=0.879,O=0.068]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.006,O=0.993]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	-
	-
	RACING
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 4 "PIVOTAL"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.030,ORG=0.903,O=0.064]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.520,O=0.473]	O	O
RACING	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.273,O=0.709]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.032,O=0.968]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.020,ORG=0.952,O=0.021]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.987,O=0.006]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.959,O=0.030]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.987,O=0.002]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.975,O=0.006]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.051,ORG=0.943,O=0.003]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.048,ORG=0.879,O=0.068]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.006,O=0.993]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	-
	-
	PIVOTAL
	RACING
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 2 "RACING" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.039,ORG=0.874,O=0.083]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.008,ORG=0.373,O=0.618]	O	O
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.052,O=0.945]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.007,O=0.993]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.021,ORG=0.951,O=0.022]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.987,O=0.006]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.959,O=0.030]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.987,O=0.002]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.975,O=0.006]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.051,ORG=0.943,O=0.003]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.048,ORG=0.879,O=0.068]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.006,O=0.993]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	-
	-
	PIVOTAL
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 3 "-" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.039,ORG=0.874,O=0.084]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.008,ORG=0.369,O=0.621]	O	O
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.047,O=0.949]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.999]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.021,ORG=0.950,O=0.022]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.987,O=0.006]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.959,O=0.030]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.987,O=0.002]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.975,O=0.006]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.051,ORG=0.943,O=0.003]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.048,ORG=0.879,O=0.068]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.006,O=0.993]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	-
	PIVOTAL
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 4 "PIVOTAL"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.039,ORG=0.874,O=0.084]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.008,ORG=0.369,O=0.621]	O	O
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.047,O=0.949]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.999]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.021,ORG=0.950,O=0.022]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.987,O=0.006]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.959,O=0.030]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.987,O=0.002]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.975,O=0.006]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.051,ORG=0.943,O=0.003]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.048,ORG=0.879,O=0.068]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.006,O=0.993]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	-
	PIVOTAL
	PIVOTAL
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 4 "PIVOTAL" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.039,ORG=0.874,O=0.084]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.008,ORG=0.369,O=0.621]	O	O
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.047,O=0.950]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.999]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.018,ORG=0.839,O=0.137]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.969,O=0.020]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.013,ORG=0.945,O=0.042]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.013,ORG=0.984,O=0.003]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.021,ORG=0.972,O=0.006]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.053,ORG=0.941,O=0.003]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.049,ORG=0.878,O=0.069]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.006,O=0.993]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	-
	PIVOTAL
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 3 "-" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.039,ORG=0.874,O=0.084]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.008,ORG=0.369,O=0.622]	O	O
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.046,O=0.950]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.839,O=0.137]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.969,O=0.020]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.013,ORG=0.945,O=0.042]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.013,ORG=0.984,O=0.003]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.021,ORG=0.972,O=0.006]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.053,ORG=0.941,O=0.003]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.049,ORG=0.878,O=0.069]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.006,O=0.993]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	PIVOTAL
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 4 "PIVOTAL"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.039,ORG=0.874,O=0.084]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.008,ORG=0.369,O=0.622]	O	O
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.046,O=0.950]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.839,O=0.137]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.969,O=0.020]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.013,ORG=0.945,O=0.042]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.013,ORG=0.984,O=0.003]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.021,ORG=0.972,O=0.006]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.053,ORG=0.941,O=0.003]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.049,ORG=0.878,O=0.069]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.006,O=0.993]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	PIVOTAL
	PIVOTAL
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 5 "ENDS"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.039,ORG=0.874,O=0.084]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.008,ORG=0.369,O=0.622]	O	O
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.046,O=0.950]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.839,O=0.137]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.969,O=0.020]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.013,ORG=0.945,O=0.042]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.013,ORG=0.984,O=0.003]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.021,ORG=0.972,O=0.006]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.053,ORG=0.941,O=0.003]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.049,ORG=0.878,O=0.069]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.006,O=0.993]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	ENDS
	PIVOTAL
	PIVOTAL
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 5 "ENDS"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.039,ORG=0.874,O=0.084]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.008,ORG=0.369,O=0.622]	O	O
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.046,O=0.950]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.839,O=0.137]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.969,O=0.020]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.013,ORG=0.945,O=0.042]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.013,ORG=0.984,O=0.003]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.021,ORG=0.972,O=0.006]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.053,ORG=0.941,O=0.003]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.049,ORG=0.878,O=0.069]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.006,O=0.993]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	ENDS
	PIVOTAL
	ENDS
	PIVOTAL
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 4 "PIVOTAL" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.039,ORG=0.874,O=0.084]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.008,ORG=0.369,O=0.622]	O	O
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.046,O=0.950]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.461,O=0.526]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.022,ORG=0.908,O=0.068]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.021,ORG=0.899,O=0.080]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.020,ORG=0.974,O=0.006]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.027,ORG=0.965,O=0.008]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.059,ORG=0.935,O=0.003]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.052,ORG=0.872,O=0.071]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.006,O=0.993]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	ENDS
	PIVOTAL
	ENDS
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 5 "ENDS" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.039,ORG=0.874,O=0.084]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.008,ORG=0.369,O=0.622]	O	O
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.046,O=0.950]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.012,ORG=0.330,O=0.656]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.646,O=0.337]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.037,ORG=0.701,O=0.261]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.046,ORG=0.936,O=0.016]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.047,ORG=0.939,O=0.014]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.079,ORG=0.914,O=0.004]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.062,ORG=0.854,O=0.080]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.006,O=0.993]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	PIVOTAL
	ENDS
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 4 "PIVOTAL" = ORG
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.039,ORG=0.874,O=0.084]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.008,ORG=0.369,O=0.622]	O	O
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.046,O=0.950]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.775,O=0.220]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.875,O=0.118]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.018,ORG=0.875,O=0.106]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.022,ORG=0.970,O=0.007]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.028,ORG=0.963,O=0.008]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.060,ORG=0.934,O=0.004]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.053,ORG=0.871,O=0.072]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.006,O=0.993]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	ENDS
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 5 "ENDS"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.039,ORG=0.874,O=0.084]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.008,ORG=0.369,O=0.622]	O	O
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.046,O=0.950]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.775,O=0.220]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.875,O=0.118]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.018,ORG=0.875,O=0.106]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.022,ORG=0.970,O=0.007]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.028,ORG=0.963,O=0.008]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.060,ORG=0.934,O=0.004]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.053,ORG=0.871,O=0.072]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.006,O=0.993]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	ENDS
	ENDS
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 6 "25-YEAR"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.039,ORG=0.874,O=0.084]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.008,ORG=0.369,O=0.622]	O	O
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.046,O=0.950]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.775,O=0.220]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.875,O=0.118]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.018,ORG=0.875,O=0.106]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.022,ORG=0.970,O=0.007]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.028,ORG=0.963,O=0.008]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.060,ORG=0.934,O=0.004]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.053,ORG=0.871,O=0.072]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.006,O=0.993]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	25-YEAR
	ENDS
	ENDS
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 6 "25-YEAR"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.039,ORG=0.874,O=0.084]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.008,ORG=0.369,O=0.622]	O	O
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.046,O=0.950]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.775,O=0.220]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.875,O=0.118]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.018,ORG=0.875,O=0.106]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.022,ORG=0.970,O=0.007]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.028,ORG=0.963,O=0.008]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.060,ORG=0.934,O=0.004]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.053,ORG=0.871,O=0.072]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.006,O=0.993]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	25-YEAR
	ENDS
	ENDS
	25-YEAR
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 5 "ENDS" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.039,ORG=0.874,O=0.084]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.008,ORG=0.369,O=0.622]	O	O
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.046,O=0.950]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.008,ORG=0.474,O=0.516]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.512,O=0.484]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.043,ORG=0.600,O=0.355]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.058,ORG=0.918,O=0.022]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.057,ORG=0.926,O=0.016]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.089,ORG=0.903,O=0.005]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.067,ORG=0.845,O=0.084]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.006,O=0.993]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	25-YEAR
	ENDS
	25-YEAR
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 6 "25-YEAR" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.039,ORG=0.874,O=0.084]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.008,ORG=0.369,O=0.622]	O	O
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.046,O=0.950]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.012,ORG=0.204,O=0.782]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.186,O=0.809]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.192,O=0.794]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.090,ORG=0.861,O=0.045]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.085,ORG=0.888,O=0.026]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.118,ORG=0.872,O=0.007]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.081,ORG=0.818,O=0.096]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.006,O=0.994]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	ENDS
	25-YEAR
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 5 "ENDS" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.039,ORG=0.874,O=0.084]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.008,ORG=0.369,O=0.622]	O	O
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.046,O=0.950]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.076,O=0.909]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.032,O=0.967]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.015,ORG=0.067,O=0.918]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.103,ORG=0.840,O=0.052]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.096,ORG=0.874,O=0.030]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.129,ORG=0.861,O=0.007]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.086,ORG=0.808,O=0.101]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.006,O=0.994]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	25-YEAR
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 6 "25-YEAR"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.039,ORG=0.874,O=0.084]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.008,ORG=0.369,O=0.622]	O	O
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.046,O=0.950]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.076,O=0.909]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.032,O=0.967]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.015,ORG=0.067,O=0.918]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.103,ORG=0.840,O=0.052]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.096,ORG=0.874,O=0.030]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.129,ORG=0.861,O=0.007]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.086,ORG=0.808,O=0.101]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.006,O=0.994]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	25-YEAR
	25-YEAR
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 7 "WAIT"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.039,ORG=0.874,O=0.084]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.008,ORG=0.369,O=0.622]	O	O
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.046,O=0.950]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.076,O=0.909]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.032,O=0.967]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.015,ORG=0.067,O=0.918]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.103,ORG=0.840,O=0.052]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.096,ORG=0.874,O=0.030]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.129,ORG=0.861,O=0.007]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.086,ORG=0.808,O=0.101]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.006,O=0.994]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	WAIT
	25-YEAR
	25-YEAR
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 7 "WAIT"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.039,ORG=0.874,O=0.084]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.008,ORG=0.369,O=0.622]	O	O
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.046,O=0.950]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.076,O=0.909]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.032,O=0.967]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.015,ORG=0.067,O=0.918]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.103,ORG=0.840,O=0.052]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.096,ORG=0.874,O=0.030]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.129,ORG=0.861,O=0.007]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.086,ORG=0.808,O=0.101]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.006,O=0.994]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	WAIT
	25-YEAR
	WAIT
	25-YEAR
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 6 "25-YEAR" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.039,ORG=0.874,O=0.084]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.008,ORG=0.369,O=0.622]	O	O
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.046,O=0.950]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.057,O=0.927]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.009,O=0.990]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.002,ORG=0.010,O=0.987]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.105,ORG=0.835,O=0.055]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.097,ORG=0.871,O=0.031]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.131,ORG=0.858,O=0.007]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.087,ORG=0.806,O=0.102]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.006,O=0.994]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	WAIT
	WAIT
	25-YEAR
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 7 "WAIT" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.039,ORG=0.874,O=0.084]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.008,ORG=0.369,O=0.622]	O	O
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.046,O=0.950]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.056,O=0.928]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.008,O=0.991]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.002,ORG=0.008,O=0.990]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.079,ORG=0.628,O=0.290]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.135,ORG=0.771,O=0.092]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.194,ORG=0.786,O=0.014]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.119,ORG=0.744,O=0.131]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.005,O=0.994]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	WAIT
	25-YEAR
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 6 "25-YEAR" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.039,ORG=0.874,O=0.084]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.008,ORG=0.369,O=0.622]	O	O
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.046,O=0.950]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.054,O=0.930]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.005,O=0.994]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.999]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.079,ORG=0.625,O=0.292]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.136,ORG=0.770,O=0.093]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.195,ORG=0.785,O=0.014]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.119,ORG=0.744,O=0.131]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.005,O=0.994]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	WAIT
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 7 "WAIT"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.039,ORG=0.874,O=0.084]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.008,ORG=0.369,O=0.622]	O	O
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.046,O=0.950]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.054,O=0.930]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.005,O=0.994]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.999]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.079,ORG=0.625,O=0.292]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.136,ORG=0.770,O=0.093]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.195,ORG=0.785,O=0.014]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.119,ORG=0.744,O=0.131]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.005,O=0.994]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	WAIT
	WAIT
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 8 "FOR"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.039,ORG=0.874,O=0.084]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.008,ORG=0.369,O=0.622]	O	O
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.046,O=0.950]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.054,O=0.930]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.005,O=0.994]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.999]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.079,ORG=0.625,O=0.292]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.136,ORG=0.770,O=0.093]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.195,ORG=0.785,O=0.014]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.119,ORG=0.744,O=0.131]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.005,O=0.994]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	WAIT
	WAIT
	FOR
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 8 "FOR"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.039,ORG=0.874,O=0.084]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.008,ORG=0.369,O=0.622]	O	O
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.046,O=0.950]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.054,O=0.930]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.005,O=0.994]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.999]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.079,ORG=0.625,O=0.292]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.136,ORG=0.770,O=0.093]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.195,ORG=0.785,O=0.014]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.119,ORG=0.744,O=0.131]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.005,O=0.994]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	FOR
	WAIT
	WAIT
	FOR
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 7 "WAIT" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.039,ORG=0.874,O=0.084]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.008,ORG=0.369,O=0.622]	O	O
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.046,O=0.950]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.053,O=0.931]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.005,O=0.994]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=0.999]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.029,ORG=0.227,O=0.743]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.208,ORG=0.578,O=0.210]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.010,LOC=0.316,ORG=0.647,O=0.028]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.008,LOC=0.179,ORG=0.625,O=0.187]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.004,O=0.995]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	FOR
	WAIT
	FOR
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 8 "FOR" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.039,ORG=0.874,O=0.084]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.008,ORG=0.369,O=0.622]	O	O
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.046,O=0.950]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.053,O=0.931]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.005,O=0.994]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.021,ORG=0.103,O=0.875]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.092,ORG=0.256,O=0.651]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.019,LOC=0.435,ORG=0.477,O=0.069]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.243,ORG=0.481,O=0.264]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.003,O=0.996]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	FOR
	WAIT
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 7 "WAIT" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.039,ORG=0.874,O=0.084]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.008,ORG=0.369,O=0.622]	O	O
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.046,O=0.950]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.053,O=0.931]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.005,O=0.994]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.016,O=0.980]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.093,ORG=0.189,O=0.716]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.021,LOC=0.469,ORG=0.435,O=0.076]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.013,LOC=0.260,ORG=0.445,O=0.282]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.003,O=0.996]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	FOR
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 8 "FOR"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.039,ORG=0.874,O=0.084]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.008,ORG=0.369,O=0.622]	O	O
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.046,O=0.950]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.053,O=0.931]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.005,O=0.994]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.016,O=0.980]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.093,ORG=0.189,O=0.716]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.021,LOC=0.469,ORG=0.435,O=0.076]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.013,LOC=0.260,ORG=0.445,O=0.282]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.003,O=0.996]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	FOR
	FOR
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 9 "TRAINER"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.039,ORG=0.874,O=0.084]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.008,ORG=0.369,O=0.622]	O	O
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.046,O=0.950]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.053,O=0.931]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.005,O=0.994]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.016,O=0.980]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.093,ORG=0.189,O=0.716]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.021,LOC=0.469,ORG=0.435,O=0.076]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.013,LOC=0.260,ORG=0.445,O=0.282]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.003,O=0.996]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	FOR
	TRAINER
	FOR
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 9 "TRAINER"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.039,ORG=0.874,O=0.084]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.008,ORG=0.369,O=0.622]	O	O
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.046,O=0.950]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.053,O=0.931]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.005,O=0.994]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.016,O=0.980]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.093,ORG=0.189,O=0.716]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.021,LOC=0.469,ORG=0.435,O=0.076]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.013,LOC=0.260,ORG=0.445,O=0.282]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.003,O=0.996]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	FOR
	TRAINER
	FOR
	TRAINER
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 8 "FOR" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.039,ORG=0.874,O=0.084]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.008,ORG=0.369,O=0.622]	O	O
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.046,O=0.950]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.053,O=0.931]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.005,O=0.994]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.002,ORG=0.004,O=0.994]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.018,ORG=0.036,O=0.946]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.026,LOC=0.518,ORG=0.359,O=0.097]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.287,ORG=0.381,O=0.317]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.003,O=0.997]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	TRAINER
	FOR
	TRAINER
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 9 "TRAINER"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.039,ORG=0.874,O=0.084]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.008,ORG=0.369,O=0.622]	O	O
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.046,O=0.950]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.053,O=0.931]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.005,O=0.994]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.002,ORG=0.004,O=0.994]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.018,ORG=0.036,O=0.946]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.026,LOC=0.518,ORG=0.359,O=0.097]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.287,ORG=0.381,O=0.317]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.003,O=0.997]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	TRAINER
	TRAINER
	FOR
	TRAINER
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 9 "TRAINER" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.039,ORG=0.874,O=0.084]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.008,ORG=0.369,O=0.622]	O	O
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.046,O=0.950]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.053,O=0.931]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.005,O=0.994]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.002,ORG=0.003,O=0.995]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.013,ORG=0.023,O=0.964]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.328,ORG=0.227,O=0.429]	O	O
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.228,ORG=0.281,O=0.477]	PER	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.002,O=0.997]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	TRAINER
	FOR
	TRAINER
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 9 "TRAINER" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.039,ORG=0.874,O=0.084]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.008,ORG=0.369,O=0.622]	O	O
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.046,O=0.950]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.053,O=0.931]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.005,O=0.994]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.002,ORG=0.001,O=0.996]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.007,ORG=0.007,O=0.986]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.092,ORG=0.064,O=0.840]	O	O
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.014,LOC=0.154,ORG=0.157,O=0.675]	PER	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	TRAINER
	FOR
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 8 "FOR" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.039,ORG=0.874,O=0.084]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.008,ORG=0.369,O=0.622]	O	O
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.046,O=0.950]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.053,O=0.931]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.005,O=0.994]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.002,ORG=0.001,O=0.997]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.090,ORG=0.059,O=0.846]	O	O
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.014,LOC=0.154,ORG=0.153,O=0.679]	PER	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	TRAINER
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 10 "PRESCOTT"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.039,ORG=0.874,O=0.084]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.008,ORG=0.369,O=0.622]	O	O
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.046,O=0.950]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.053,O=0.931]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.005,O=0.994]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.002,ORG=0.001,O=0.997]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.090,ORG=0.059,O=0.846]	O	O
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.014,LOC=0.154,ORG=0.153,O=0.679]	PER	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	TRAINER
	PRESCOTT
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 10 "PRESCOTT"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.039,ORG=0.874,O=0.084]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.008,ORG=0.369,O=0.622]	O	O
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.046,O=0.950]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.053,O=0.931]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.005,O=0.994]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.002,ORG=0.001,O=0.997]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.090,ORG=0.059,O=0.846]	O	O
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.014,LOC=0.154,ORG=0.153,O=0.679]	PER	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	PRESCOTT
	TRAINER
	PRESCOTT
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 10 "PRESCOTT"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.039,ORG=0.874,O=0.084]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.008,ORG=0.369,O=0.622]	O	O
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.046,O=0.950]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.053,O=0.931]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.005,O=0.994]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.002,ORG=0.001,O=0.997]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.090,ORG=0.059,O=0.846]	O	O
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.014,LOC=0.154,ORG=0.153,O=0.679]	PER	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	PRESCOTT
	TRAINER
	PRESCOTT
	PRESCOTT
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 9 "TRAINER" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.039,ORG=0.874,O=0.084]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.008,ORG=0.369,O=0.622]	O	O
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.046,O=0.950]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.053,O=0.931]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.005,O=0.994]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.002,ORG=0.001,O=0.997]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.000,O=0.999]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.015,ORG=0.010,O=0.975]	O	O
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.014,LOC=0.131,ORG=0.116,O=0.740]	PER	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.999]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	PRESCOTT
	PRESCOTT
	PRESCOTT
-----------
Move choice:
io.hybridcrowd.gameplay.Game$Wait@837
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.039,ORG=0.874,O=0.084]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.008,ORG=0.369,O=0.622]	O	O
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.046,O=0.950]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.053,O=0.931]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.005,O=0.994]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.002,ORG=0.001,O=0.997]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.000,O=0.999]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.015,ORG=0.010,O=0.975]	O	O
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.014,LOC=0.131,ORG=0.116,O=0.740]	PER	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.999]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	PRESCOTT
	PRESCOTT
	PRESCOTT
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 10 "PRESCOTT" = PER
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.039,ORG=0.874,O=0.084]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.008,ORG=0.369,O=0.622]	O	O
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.046,O=0.950]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.053,O=0.931]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.005,O=0.994]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.002,ORG=0.001,O=0.997]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.000,O=0.999]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.009,O=0.974]	O	O
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.088,LOC=0.121,ORG=0.107,O=0.684]	PER	O
.	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	PRESCOTT
	PRESCOTT
-----------
Move choice:
io.hybridcrowd.gameplay.Game$Wait@841
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.039,ORG=0.874,O=0.084]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.008,ORG=0.369,O=0.622]	O	O
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.046,O=0.950]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.053,O=0.931]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.005,O=0.994]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.002,ORG=0.001,O=0.997]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.000,O=0.999]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.009,O=0.974]	O	O
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.088,LOC=0.121,ORG=0.107,O=0.684]	PER	O
.	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	PRESCOTT
	PRESCOTT
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 10 "PRESCOTT" = ORG
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.039,ORG=0.874,O=0.084]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.008,ORG=0.369,O=0.622]	O	O
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.046,O=0.950]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.053,O=0.931]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.005,O=0.994]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.002,ORG=0.001,O=0.997]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.999]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.012,ORG=0.036,O=0.950]	O	O
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.053,LOC=0.073,ORG=0.457,O=0.416]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.003,O=0.996]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	PRESCOTT
-----------
Move choice:
io.hybridcrowd.gameplay.Game$Wait@868
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.039,ORG=0.874,O=0.084]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.008,ORG=0.369,O=0.622]	O	O
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.046,O=0.950]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.053,O=0.931]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.005,O=0.994]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.002,ORG=0.001,O=0.997]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.999]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.012,ORG=0.036,O=0.950]	O	O
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.053,LOC=0.073,ORG=0.457,O=0.416]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.003,O=0.996]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
	PRESCOTT
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 10 "PRESCOTT" = PER
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.039,ORG=0.874,O=0.084]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.008,ORG=0.369,O=0.622]	O	O
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.046,O=0.950]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.053,O=0.931]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.005,O=0.994]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.002,ORG=0.001,O=0.997]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.001,O=0.999]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.011,ORG=0.028,O=0.955]	O	O
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.283,LOC=0.056,ORG=0.346,O=0.315]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.002,O=0.996]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
-----------
Move choice:
io.hybridcrowd.gameplay.Game$TurnIn@880
