Game Results:

TOKEN	TAG	GUESS
QUERIES
-------------
REUTER	PER	ORG	2
HORSE	O	ORG	0
RACING	O	O	4
-	O	O	0
PIVOTAL	PER	O	2
ENDS	O	O	2
25-YEAR	O	O	2
WAIT	O	O	3
FOR	O	O	2
TRAINER	O	O	4
PRESCOTT	PER	PER	5
.	O	O	0

Game History:

-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.084,ORG=0.890,O=0.012]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.009,ORG=0.987,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.040,ORG=0.931,O=0.024]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.056,O=0.944]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.054,ORG=0.900,O=0.033]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.026,ORG=0.953,O=0.019]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.056,ORG=0.876,O=0.066]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.068,ORG=0.920,O=0.010]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.097,ORG=0.882,O=0.020]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.172,ORG=0.813,O=0.009]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.008,LOC=0.105,ORG=0.736,O=0.152]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.004,O=0.995]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 0
Current in-flight queries: 
-----------
Move choice:
Making job posting
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.084,ORG=0.890,O=0.012]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.009,ORG=0.987,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.040,ORG=0.931,O=0.024]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.056,O=0.944]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.054,ORG=0.900,O=0.033]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.026,ORG=0.953,O=0.019]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.056,ORG=0.876,O=0.066]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.068,ORG=0.920,O=0.010]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.097,ORG=0.882,O=0.020]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.172,ORG=0.813,O=0.009]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.008,LOC=0.105,ORG=0.736,O=0.152]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.004,O=0.995]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 1
Current available humans: 0
Current in-flight queries: 
-----------
Next event:
io.hybridcrowd.gameplay.Game$HumanArrival@0
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.084,ORG=0.890,O=0.012]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.009,ORG=0.987,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.040,ORG=0.931,O=0.024]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.056,O=0.944]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.054,ORG=0.900,O=0.033]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.026,ORG=0.953,O=0.019]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.056,ORG=0.876,O=0.066]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.068,ORG=0.920,O=0.010]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.097,ORG=0.882,O=0.020]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.172,ORG=0.813,O=0.009]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.008,LOC=0.105,ORG=0.736,O=0.152]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.004,O=0.995]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 1
Current in-flight queries: 
-----------
Move choice:
Making job posting
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.084,ORG=0.890,O=0.012]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.009,ORG=0.987,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.040,ORG=0.931,O=0.024]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.056,O=0.944]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.054,ORG=0.900,O=0.033]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.026,ORG=0.953,O=0.019]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.056,ORG=0.876,O=0.066]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.068,ORG=0.920,O=0.010]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.097,ORG=0.882,O=0.020]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.172,ORG=0.813,O=0.009]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.008,LOC=0.105,ORG=0.736,O=0.152]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.004,O=0.995]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 1
Current available humans: 1
Current in-flight queries: 
-----------
Next event:
io.hybridcrowd.gameplay.Game$HumanArrival@0
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.084,ORG=0.890,O=0.012]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.009,ORG=0.987,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.040,ORG=0.931,O=0.024]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.056,O=0.944]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.054,ORG=0.900,O=0.033]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.026,ORG=0.953,O=0.019]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.056,ORG=0.876,O=0.066]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.068,ORG=0.920,O=0.010]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.097,ORG=0.882,O=0.020]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.172,ORG=0.813,O=0.009]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.008,LOC=0.105,ORG=0.736,O=0.152]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.004,O=0.995]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 2
Current in-flight queries: 
-----------
Move choice:
Making job posting
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.084,ORG=0.890,O=0.012]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.009,ORG=0.987,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.040,ORG=0.931,O=0.024]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.056,O=0.944]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.054,ORG=0.900,O=0.033]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.026,ORG=0.953,O=0.019]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.056,ORG=0.876,O=0.066]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.068,ORG=0.920,O=0.010]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.097,ORG=0.882,O=0.020]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.172,ORG=0.813,O=0.009]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.008,LOC=0.105,ORG=0.736,O=0.152]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.004,O=0.995]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 1
Current available humans: 2
Current in-flight queries: 
-----------
Next event:
io.hybridcrowd.gameplay.Game$HumanArrival@2
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.084,ORG=0.890,O=0.012]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.009,ORG=0.987,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.040,ORG=0.931,O=0.024]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.056,O=0.944]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.054,ORG=0.900,O=0.033]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.026,ORG=0.953,O=0.019]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.056,ORG=0.876,O=0.066]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.068,ORG=0.920,O=0.010]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.097,ORG=0.882,O=0.020]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.172,ORG=0.813,O=0.009]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.008,LOC=0.105,ORG=0.736,O=0.152]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.004,O=0.995]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
-----------
Move choice:
Making job posting
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.084,ORG=0.890,O=0.012]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.009,ORG=0.987,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.040,ORG=0.931,O=0.024]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.056,O=0.944]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.054,ORG=0.900,O=0.033]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.026,ORG=0.953,O=0.019]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.056,ORG=0.876,O=0.066]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.068,ORG=0.920,O=0.010]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.097,ORG=0.882,O=0.020]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.172,ORG=0.813,O=0.009]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.008,LOC=0.105,ORG=0.736,O=0.152]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.004,O=0.995]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 1
Current available humans: 3
Current in-flight queries: 
-----------
Next event:
io.hybridcrowd.gameplay.Game$HumanArrival@6
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.084,ORG=0.890,O=0.012]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.009,ORG=0.987,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.040,ORG=0.931,O=0.024]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.056,O=0.944]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.054,ORG=0.900,O=0.033]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.026,ORG=0.953,O=0.019]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.056,ORG=0.876,O=0.066]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.068,ORG=0.920,O=0.010]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.097,ORG=0.882,O=0.020]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.172,ORG=0.813,O=0.009]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.008,LOC=0.105,ORG=0.736,O=0.152]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.004,O=0.995]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
-----------
Move choice:
Making job posting
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.084,ORG=0.890,O=0.012]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.009,ORG=0.987,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.040,ORG=0.931,O=0.024]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.056,O=0.944]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.054,ORG=0.900,O=0.033]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.026,ORG=0.953,O=0.019]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.056,ORG=0.876,O=0.066]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.068,ORG=0.920,O=0.010]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.097,ORG=0.882,O=0.020]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.172,ORG=0.813,O=0.009]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.008,LOC=0.105,ORG=0.736,O=0.152]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.004,O=0.995]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 1
Current available humans: 4
Current in-flight queries: 
-----------
Next event:
io.hybridcrowd.gameplay.Game$HumanArrival@9
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.084,ORG=0.890,O=0.012]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.009,ORG=0.987,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.040,ORG=0.931,O=0.024]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.056,O=0.944]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.054,ORG=0.900,O=0.033]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.026,ORG=0.953,O=0.019]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.056,ORG=0.876,O=0.066]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.068,ORG=0.920,O=0.010]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.097,ORG=0.882,O=0.020]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.172,ORG=0.813,O=0.009]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.008,LOC=0.105,ORG=0.736,O=0.152]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.004,O=0.995]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 9 "TRAINER"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.084,ORG=0.890,O=0.012]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.009,ORG=0.987,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.040,ORG=0.931,O=0.024]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.056,O=0.944]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.054,ORG=0.900,O=0.033]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.026,ORG=0.953,O=0.019]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.056,ORG=0.876,O=0.066]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.068,ORG=0.920,O=0.010]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.097,ORG=0.882,O=0.020]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.172,ORG=0.813,O=0.009]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.008,LOC=0.105,ORG=0.736,O=0.152]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.004,O=0.995]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
	TRAINER
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 4 "PIVOTAL"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.084,ORG=0.890,O=0.012]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.009,ORG=0.987,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.040,ORG=0.931,O=0.024]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.056,O=0.944]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.054,ORG=0.900,O=0.033]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.026,ORG=0.953,O=0.019]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.056,ORG=0.876,O=0.066]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.068,ORG=0.920,O=0.010]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.097,ORG=0.882,O=0.020]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.172,ORG=0.813,O=0.009]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.008,LOC=0.105,ORG=0.736,O=0.152]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.004,O=0.995]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
	PIVOTAL
	TRAINER
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 10 "PRESCOTT"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.084,ORG=0.890,O=0.012]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.009,ORG=0.987,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.040,ORG=0.931,O=0.024]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.056,O=0.944]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.054,ORG=0.900,O=0.033]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.026,ORG=0.953,O=0.019]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.056,ORG=0.876,O=0.066]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.068,ORG=0.920,O=0.010]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.097,ORG=0.882,O=0.020]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.172,ORG=0.813,O=0.009]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.008,LOC=0.105,ORG=0.736,O=0.152]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.004,O=0.995]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
	PRESCOTT
	PIVOTAL
	TRAINER
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 9 "TRAINER" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.084,ORG=0.890,O=0.012]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.009,ORG=0.987,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.040,ORG=0.931,O=0.024]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.056,O=0.944]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.055,ORG=0.899,O=0.034]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.027,ORG=0.951,O=0.019]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.059,ORG=0.872,O=0.068]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.072,ORG=0.914,O=0.012]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.101,ORG=0.868,O=0.030]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.163,ORG=0.773,O=0.059]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.008,LOC=0.105,ORG=0.705,O=0.182]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.004,O=0.995]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
	PRESCOTT
	PIVOTAL
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 4 "PIVOTAL" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.084,ORG=0.889,O=0.012]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.009,ORG=0.987,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.040,ORG=0.931,O=0.024]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.046,O=0.953]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.010,LOC=0.046,ORG=0.748,O=0.196]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.036,ORG=0.907,O=0.053]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.071,ORG=0.840,O=0.089]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.085,ORG=0.898,O=0.015]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.111,ORG=0.856,O=0.032]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.172,ORG=0.763,O=0.060]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.008,LOC=0.108,ORG=0.698,O=0.186]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.004,O=0.995]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
	PRESCOTT
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 9 "TRAINER"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.084,ORG=0.889,O=0.012]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.009,ORG=0.987,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.040,ORG=0.931,O=0.024]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.046,O=0.953]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.010,LOC=0.046,ORG=0.748,O=0.196]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.036,ORG=0.907,O=0.053]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.071,ORG=0.840,O=0.089]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.085,ORG=0.898,O=0.015]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.111,ORG=0.856,O=0.032]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.172,ORG=0.763,O=0.060]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.008,LOC=0.108,ORG=0.698,O=0.186]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.004,O=0.995]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
	PRESCOTT
	TRAINER
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 6 "25-YEAR"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.084,ORG=0.889,O=0.012]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.009,ORG=0.987,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.040,ORG=0.931,O=0.024]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.046,O=0.953]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.010,LOC=0.046,ORG=0.748,O=0.196]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.036,ORG=0.907,O=0.053]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.071,ORG=0.840,O=0.089]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.085,ORG=0.898,O=0.015]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.111,ORG=0.856,O=0.032]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.006,LOC=0.172,ORG=0.763,O=0.060]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.008,LOC=0.108,ORG=0.698,O=0.186]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.004,O=0.995]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
	25-YEAR
	PRESCOTT
	TRAINER
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 9 "TRAINER" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.084,ORG=0.889,O=0.012]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.009,ORG=0.987,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.040,ORG=0.931,O=0.024]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.046,O=0.954]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.010,LOC=0.049,ORG=0.739,O=0.202]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.042,ORG=0.895,O=0.059]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.085,ORG=0.814,O=0.100]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.110,ORG=0.864,O=0.024]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.133,ORG=0.782,O=0.084]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.126,ORG=0.561,O=0.308]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.009,LOC=0.107,ORG=0.548,O=0.337]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.003,O=0.996]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
	25-YEAR
	PRESCOTT
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 5 "ENDS"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.084,ORG=0.889,O=0.012]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.009,ORG=0.987,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.040,ORG=0.931,O=0.024]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.046,O=0.954]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.010,LOC=0.049,ORG=0.739,O=0.202]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.042,ORG=0.895,O=0.059]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.085,ORG=0.814,O=0.100]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.110,ORG=0.864,O=0.024]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.133,ORG=0.782,O=0.084]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.126,ORG=0.561,O=0.308]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.009,LOC=0.107,ORG=0.548,O=0.337]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.003,O=0.996]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
	25-YEAR
	PRESCOTT
	ENDS
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 6 "25-YEAR" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.084,ORG=0.889,O=0.012]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.009,ORG=0.987,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.040,ORG=0.930,O=0.024]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.040,O=0.959]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.064,ORG=0.641,O=0.284]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.060,ORG=0.761,O=0.173]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.053,ORG=0.509,O=0.437]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.183,ORG=0.738,O=0.074]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.193,ORG=0.685,O=0.120]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.155,ORG=0.497,O=0.344]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.009,LOC=0.122,ORG=0.500,O=0.369]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.003,O=0.996]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
	PRESCOTT
	ENDS
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 10 "PRESCOTT" = PER
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.084,ORG=0.889,O=0.012]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.009,ORG=0.987,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.040,ORG=0.930,O=0.024]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.040,O=0.959]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.064,ORG=0.640,O=0.284]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.061,ORG=0.760,O=0.174]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.054,ORG=0.508,O=0.438]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.185,ORG=0.735,O=0.075]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.195,ORG=0.681,O=0.122]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.011,LOC=0.155,ORG=0.486,O=0.348]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.059,LOC=0.116,ORG=0.474,O=0.351]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.003,O=0.996]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
	ENDS
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 7 "WAIT"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.084,ORG=0.889,O=0.012]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.009,ORG=0.987,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.040,ORG=0.930,O=0.024]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.040,O=0.959]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.064,ORG=0.640,O=0.284]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.061,ORG=0.760,O=0.174]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.054,ORG=0.508,O=0.438]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.185,ORG=0.735,O=0.075]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.195,ORG=0.681,O=0.122]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.011,LOC=0.155,ORG=0.486,O=0.348]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.059,LOC=0.116,ORG=0.474,O=0.351]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.003,O=0.996]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
	WAIT
	ENDS
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 8 "FOR"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.084,ORG=0.889,O=0.012]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.009,ORG=0.987,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.040,ORG=0.930,O=0.024]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.040,O=0.959]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.064,ORG=0.640,O=0.284]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.061,ORG=0.760,O=0.174]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.054,ORG=0.508,O=0.438]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.185,ORG=0.735,O=0.075]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.195,ORG=0.681,O=0.122]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.011,LOC=0.155,ORG=0.486,O=0.348]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.059,LOC=0.116,ORG=0.474,O=0.351]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.003,O=0.996]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
	WAIT
	ENDS
	FOR
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 10 "PRESCOTT"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.084,ORG=0.889,O=0.012]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.009,ORG=0.987,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.040,ORG=0.930,O=0.024]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.040,O=0.959]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.064,ORG=0.640,O=0.284]	PER	ORG
ENDS	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.061,ORG=0.760,O=0.174]	O	ORG
25-YEAR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.054,ORG=0.508,O=0.438]	O	ORG
WAIT	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.185,ORG=0.735,O=0.075]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.195,ORG=0.681,O=0.122]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.011,LOC=0.155,ORG=0.486,O=0.348]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.059,LOC=0.116,ORG=0.474,O=0.351]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.003,O=0.996]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
	PRESCOTT
	WAIT
	ENDS
	FOR
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 5 "ENDS" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.084,ORG=0.889,O=0.012]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.009,ORG=0.986,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.041,ORG=0.929,O=0.025]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.023,O=0.977]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.078,ORG=0.354,O=0.556]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.030,ORG=0.372,O=0.595]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.051,ORG=0.266,O=0.682]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.007,LOC=0.253,ORG=0.628,O=0.112]	O	ORG
FOR	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.249,ORG=0.598,O=0.151]	O	ORG
TRAINER	[PER=0.011,LOC=0.180,ORG=0.432,O=0.377]	O	ORG
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.061,LOC=0.129,ORG=0.434,O=0.376]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.003,O=0.997]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
	PRESCOTT
	WAIT
	FOR
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 7 "WAIT" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.084,ORG=0.889,O=0.012]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.009,ORG=0.986,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.041,ORG=0.929,O=0.025]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.019,O=0.980]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.083,ORG=0.297,O=0.607]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.030,ORG=0.295,O=0.672]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.038,ORG=0.164,O=0.797]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.151,ORG=0.375,O=0.470]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.251,ORG=0.421,O=0.325]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.011,LOC=0.189,ORG=0.318,O=0.483]	O	O
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.065,LOC=0.140,ORG=0.351,O=0.445]	PER	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.002,O=0.997]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
	PRESCOTT
	FOR
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 4 "PIVOTAL"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.084,ORG=0.889,O=0.012]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.009,ORG=0.986,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.041,ORG=0.929,O=0.025]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.019,O=0.980]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.083,ORG=0.297,O=0.607]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.030,ORG=0.295,O=0.672]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.038,ORG=0.164,O=0.797]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.151,ORG=0.375,O=0.470]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.251,ORG=0.421,O=0.325]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.011,LOC=0.189,ORG=0.318,O=0.483]	O	O
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.065,LOC=0.140,ORG=0.351,O=0.445]	PER	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.002,O=0.997]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
	PRESCOTT
	PIVOTAL
	FOR
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 8 "FOR" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.084,ORG=0.889,O=0.012]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.009,ORG=0.986,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.041,ORG=0.928,O=0.025]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.017,O=0.983]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.088,ORG=0.252,O=0.648]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.032,ORG=0.233,O=0.733]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.033,ORG=0.082,O=0.884]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.109,ORG=0.171,O=0.716]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.085,ORG=0.143,O=0.771]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.010,LOC=0.135,ORG=0.138,O=0.717]	O	O
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.072,LOC=0.133,ORG=0.220,O=0.574]	PER	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
	PRESCOTT
	PIVOTAL
-----------
Move choice:
io.hybridcrowd.gameplay.Game$Wait@1c6
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.084,ORG=0.889,O=0.012]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.009,ORG=0.986,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.041,ORG=0.928,O=0.025]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.017,O=0.983]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.088,ORG=0.252,O=0.648]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.032,ORG=0.233,O=0.733]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.033,ORG=0.082,O=0.884]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.109,ORG=0.171,O=0.716]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.085,ORG=0.143,O=0.771]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.010,LOC=0.135,ORG=0.138,O=0.717]	O	O
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.072,LOC=0.133,ORG=0.220,O=0.574]	PER	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
	PRESCOTT
	PIVOTAL
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 4 "PIVOTAL" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.084,ORG=0.889,O=0.012]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.986,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.042,ORG=0.928,O=0.025]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.004,O=0.995]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.018,ORG=0.052,O=0.928]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.024,ORG=0.090,O=0.884]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.030,ORG=0.037,O=0.932]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.111,ORG=0.138,O=0.748]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.086,ORG=0.122,O=0.791]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.010,LOC=0.136,ORG=0.124,O=0.729]	O	O
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.072,LOC=0.135,ORG=0.211,O=0.582]	PER	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
	PRESCOTT
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 5 "ENDS"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.084,ORG=0.889,O=0.012]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.986,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.042,ORG=0.928,O=0.025]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.004,O=0.995]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.018,ORG=0.052,O=0.928]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.024,ORG=0.090,O=0.884]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.030,ORG=0.037,O=0.932]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.111,ORG=0.138,O=0.748]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.086,ORG=0.122,O=0.791]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.010,LOC=0.136,ORG=0.124,O=0.729]	O	O
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.072,LOC=0.135,ORG=0.211,O=0.582]	PER	O
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.998]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
	PRESCOTT
	ENDS
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 10 "PRESCOTT" = ORG
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.084,ORG=0.889,O=0.012]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.986,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.042,ORG=0.928,O=0.025]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.005,O=0.995]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.018,ORG=0.058,O=0.922]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.023,ORG=0.105,O=0.869]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.029,ORG=0.058,O=0.912]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.099,ORG=0.231,O=0.667]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.071,ORG=0.257,O=0.671]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.007,LOC=0.099,ORG=0.335,O=0.560]	O	O
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.032,LOC=0.060,ORG=0.651,O=0.257]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.004,O=0.995]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
	ENDS
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 9 "TRAINER"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.084,ORG=0.889,O=0.012]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.986,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.042,ORG=0.928,O=0.025]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.005,O=0.995]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.018,ORG=0.058,O=0.922]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.023,ORG=0.105,O=0.869]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.029,ORG=0.058,O=0.912]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.099,ORG=0.231,O=0.667]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.071,ORG=0.257,O=0.671]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.007,LOC=0.099,ORG=0.335,O=0.560]	O	O
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.032,LOC=0.060,ORG=0.651,O=0.257]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.004,O=0.995]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
	ENDS
	TRAINER
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 5 "ENDS" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.084,ORG=0.889,O=0.012]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.986,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.042,ORG=0.928,O=0.025]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.002,O=0.997]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.021,O=0.961]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.017,O=0.979]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.026,ORG=0.021,O=0.953]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.100,ORG=0.204,O=0.692]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.072,ORG=0.237,O=0.690]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.007,LOC=0.101,ORG=0.320,O=0.573]	O	O
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.033,LOC=0.061,ORG=0.644,O=0.263]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.004,O=0.996]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
	TRAINER
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 8 "FOR"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.084,ORG=0.889,O=0.012]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.986,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.042,ORG=0.928,O=0.025]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.002,O=0.997]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.021,O=0.961]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.017,O=0.979]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.026,ORG=0.021,O=0.953]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.100,ORG=0.204,O=0.692]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.072,ORG=0.237,O=0.690]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.007,LOC=0.101,ORG=0.320,O=0.573]	O	O
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.033,LOC=0.061,ORG=0.644,O=0.263]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.004,O=0.996]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
	FOR
	TRAINER
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 9 "TRAINER" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.084,ORG=0.889,O=0.012]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.986,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.042,ORG=0.927,O=0.025]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.002,O=0.997]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.019,O=0.963]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.014,O=0.982]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.025,ORG=0.011,O=0.963]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.102,ORG=0.099,O=0.795]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.057,ORG=0.080,O=0.862]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.023,ORG=0.072,O=0.904]	O	O
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.039,LOC=0.056,ORG=0.528,O=0.376]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.003,O=0.996]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
	FOR
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 10 "PRESCOTT"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.084,ORG=0.889,O=0.012]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.986,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.042,ORG=0.927,O=0.025]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.002,O=0.997]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.019,O=0.963]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.014,O=0.982]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.025,ORG=0.011,O=0.963]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.102,ORG=0.099,O=0.795]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.057,ORG=0.080,O=0.862]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.023,ORG=0.072,O=0.904]	O	O
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.039,LOC=0.056,ORG=0.528,O=0.376]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.003,O=0.996]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
	FOR
	PRESCOTT
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 10 "PRESCOTT"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.084,ORG=0.889,O=0.012]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.986,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.042,ORG=0.927,O=0.025]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.002,O=0.997]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.019,O=0.963]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.014,O=0.982]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.025,ORG=0.011,O=0.963]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.102,ORG=0.099,O=0.795]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.057,ORG=0.080,O=0.862]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.023,ORG=0.072,O=0.904]	O	O
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.039,LOC=0.056,ORG=0.528,O=0.376]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.003,O=0.996]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
	FOR
	PRESCOTT
	PRESCOTT
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 8 "FOR" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.084,ORG=0.889,O=0.012]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.986,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.042,ORG=0.927,O=0.025]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.002,O=0.997]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.019,O=0.963]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.012,O=0.984]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.023,ORG=0.007,O=0.969]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.089,ORG=0.054,O=0.854]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.009,ORG=0.013,O=0.978]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.018,ORG=0.033,O=0.948]	O	O
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.041,LOC=0.057,ORG=0.510,O=0.392]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.003,O=0.996]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
	PRESCOTT
	PRESCOTT
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 7 "WAIT"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.084,ORG=0.889,O=0.012]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.986,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.042,ORG=0.927,O=0.025]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.002,O=0.997]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.019,O=0.963]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.012,O=0.984]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.023,ORG=0.007,O=0.969]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.089,ORG=0.054,O=0.854]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.009,ORG=0.013,O=0.978]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.018,ORG=0.033,O=0.948]	O	O
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.041,LOC=0.057,ORG=0.510,O=0.392]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.003,O=0.996]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
	PRESCOTT
	WAIT
	PRESCOTT
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 10 "PRESCOTT" = PER
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.084,ORG=0.889,O=0.012]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.986,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.042,ORG=0.927,O=0.025]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.002,O=0.997]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.019,O=0.963]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.012,O=0.984]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.023,ORG=0.007,O=0.969]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.089,ORG=0.053,O=0.855]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.009,ORG=0.012,O=0.979]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.017,ORG=0.028,O=0.950]	O	O
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.229,LOC=0.046,ORG=0.410,O=0.315]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.003,O=0.996]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
	PRESCOTT
	WAIT
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 2 "RACING"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.084,ORG=0.889,O=0.012]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.986,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.042,ORG=0.927,O=0.025]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.002,O=0.997]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.019,O=0.963]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.012,O=0.984]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.023,ORG=0.007,O=0.969]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.089,ORG=0.053,O=0.855]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.009,ORG=0.012,O=0.979]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.017,ORG=0.028,O=0.950]	O	O
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.229,LOC=0.046,ORG=0.410,O=0.315]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.003,O=0.996]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
	PRESCOTT
	WAIT
	RACING
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 0 "REUTER"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.084,ORG=0.889,O=0.012]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.986,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.042,ORG=0.927,O=0.025]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.002,O=0.997]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.019,O=0.963]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.012,O=0.984]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.023,ORG=0.007,O=0.969]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.089,ORG=0.053,O=0.855]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.009,ORG=0.012,O=0.979]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.017,ORG=0.028,O=0.950]	O	O
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.229,LOC=0.046,ORG=0.410,O=0.315]	PER	ORG
.	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.003,O=0.996]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
	PRESCOTT
	WAIT
	REUTER
	RACING
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 10 "PRESCOTT" = PER
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.015,LOC=0.084,ORG=0.889,O=0.012]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.986,O=0.001]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.042,ORG=0.927,O=0.025]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.002,O=0.997]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.019,O=0.963]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.012,O=0.984]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.023,ORG=0.007,O=0.970]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.089,ORG=0.051,O=0.857]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.009,ORG=0.009,O=0.982]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.014,O=0.957]	O	O
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.675,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.173,O=0.133]	PER	PER
.	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.995]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
	WAIT
	REUTER
	RACING
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 2 "RACING" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.089,ORG=0.883,O=0.012]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.978,O=0.002]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.036,ORG=0.806,O=0.153]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.002,O=0.998]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.019,O=0.963]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.012,O=0.984]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.023,ORG=0.007,O=0.970]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.089,ORG=0.051,O=0.857]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.009,ORG=0.009,O=0.982]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.014,O=0.957]	O	O
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.675,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.173,O=0.133]	PER	PER
.	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.995]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
	WAIT
	REUTER
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 7 "WAIT" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.089,ORG=0.883,O=0.012]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.978,O=0.002]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.036,ORG=0.806,O=0.153]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.002,O=0.998]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.018,O=0.964]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.011,O=0.986]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.003,O=0.981]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.008,O=0.977]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.004,O=0.990]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.012,O=0.960]	O	O
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.676,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.172,O=0.133]	PER	PER
.	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.995]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
	REUTER
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 2 "RACING"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.089,ORG=0.883,O=0.012]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.978,O=0.002]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.036,ORG=0.806,O=0.153]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.002,O=0.998]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.018,O=0.964]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.011,O=0.986]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.003,O=0.981]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.008,O=0.977]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.004,O=0.990]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.012,O=0.960]	O	O
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.676,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.172,O=0.133]	PER	PER
.	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.995]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
	REUTER
	RACING
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 10 "PRESCOTT"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.016,LOC=0.089,ORG=0.883,O=0.012]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.978,O=0.002]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.036,ORG=0.806,O=0.153]	O	ORG
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.002,O=0.998]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.018,O=0.964]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.011,O=0.986]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.003,O=0.981]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.008,O=0.977]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.004,O=0.990]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.012,O=0.960]	O	O
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.676,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.172,O=0.133]	PER	PER
.	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.995]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
	PRESCOTT
	REUTER
	RACING
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 2 "RACING" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.019,LOC=0.104,ORG=0.864,O=0.013]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.010,LOC=0.030,ORG=0.953,O=0.007]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.420,O=0.559]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.999]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.017,O=0.965]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.010,O=0.986]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.003,O=0.981]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.008,O=0.977]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.004,O=0.990]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.012,O=0.960]	O	O
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.676,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.172,O=0.133]	PER	PER
.	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.995]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
	PRESCOTT
	REUTER
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 0 "REUTER"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.019,LOC=0.104,ORG=0.864,O=0.013]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.010,LOC=0.030,ORG=0.953,O=0.007]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.420,O=0.559]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.999]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.017,O=0.965]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.010,O=0.986]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.003,O=0.981]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.008,O=0.977]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.004,O=0.990]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.012,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.012,O=0.960]	O	O
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.676,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.172,O=0.133]	PER	PER
.	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.995]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
	PRESCOTT
	REUTER
	REUTER
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 10 "PRESCOTT" = PER
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.019,LOC=0.104,ORG=0.864,O=0.013]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.010,LOC=0.030,ORG=0.953,O=0.007]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.420,O=0.559]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.999]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.017,O=0.965]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.010,O=0.986]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.003,O=0.981]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.008,O=0.977]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.003,O=0.991]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.017,LOC=0.015,ORG=0.006,O=0.962]	O	O
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.936,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.034,O=0.026]	PER	PER
.	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.994]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
	REUTER
	REUTER
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 2 "RACING"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.019,LOC=0.104,ORG=0.864,O=0.013]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.010,LOC=0.030,ORG=0.953,O=0.007]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.420,O=0.559]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.999]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.017,O=0.965]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.010,O=0.986]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.003,O=0.981]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.008,O=0.977]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.003,O=0.991]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.017,LOC=0.015,ORG=0.006,O=0.962]	O	O
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.936,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.034,O=0.026]	PER	PER
.	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.994]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
	RACING
	REUTER
	REUTER
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 0 "REUTER" = ORG
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.017,ORG=0.978,O=0.002]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.007,ORG=0.987,O=0.002]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.017,ORG=0.434,O=0.547]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.999]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.018,O=0.965]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.010,O=0.986]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.003,O=0.981]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.008,O=0.977]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.003,O=0.991]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.017,LOC=0.015,ORG=0.006,O=0.962]	O	O
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.936,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.034,O=0.026]	PER	PER
.	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.994]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
	RACING
	REUTER
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 2 "RACING"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.017,ORG=0.978,O=0.002]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.003,LOC=0.007,ORG=0.987,O=0.002]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.017,ORG=0.434,O=0.547]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.999]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.018,O=0.965]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.010,O=0.986]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.003,O=0.981]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.008,O=0.977]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.003,O=0.991]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.017,LOC=0.015,ORG=0.006,O=0.962]	O	O
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.936,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.034,O=0.026]	PER	PER
.	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.994]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
	RACING
	REUTER
	RACING
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 2 "RACING" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.975,O=0.002]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.981,O=0.004]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.101,O=0.894]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.017,O=0.965]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.010,O=0.986]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.003,O=0.981]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.008,O=0.977]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.003,O=0.991]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.017,LOC=0.015,ORG=0.006,O=0.962]	O	O
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.936,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.034,O=0.026]	PER	PER
.	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.994]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
	REUTER
	RACING
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 7 "WAIT"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.019,ORG=0.975,O=0.002]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.010,ORG=0.981,O=0.004]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.101,O=0.894]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.017,O=0.965]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.010,O=0.986]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.003,O=0.981]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.008,O=0.977]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.003,O=0.991]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.017,LOC=0.015,ORG=0.006,O=0.962]	O	O
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.936,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.034,O=0.026]	PER	PER
.	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.994]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
	REUTER
	RACING
	WAIT
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 2 "RACING" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.020,ORG=0.974,O=0.002]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.011,ORG=0.980,O=0.004]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.016,O=0.983]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.017,O=0.965]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.010,O=0.986]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.003,O=0.981]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.008,O=0.977]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.003,O=0.991]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.017,LOC=0.015,ORG=0.006,O=0.962]	O	O
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.936,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.034,O=0.026]	PER	PER
.	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.994]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
	REUTER
	WAIT
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 0 "REUTER" = ORG
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.996,O=0.000]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.988,O=0.003]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.016,O=0.983]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.017,O=0.965]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.010,O=0.986]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.003,O=0.981]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.008,O=0.977]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.003,O=0.991]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.017,LOC=0.015,ORG=0.006,O=0.962]	O	O
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.936,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.034,O=0.026]	PER	PER
.	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.994]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
	WAIT
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 6 "25-YEAR"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.996,O=0.000]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.988,O=0.003]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.016,O=0.983]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.017,O=0.965]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.010,O=0.986]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.003,O=0.981]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.008,O=0.977]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.006,ORG=0.003,O=0.991]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.017,LOC=0.015,ORG=0.006,O=0.962]	O	O
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.936,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.034,O=0.026]	PER	PER
.	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.994]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
	25-YEAR
	WAIT
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 7 "WAIT" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.996,O=0.000]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.988,O=0.003]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.016,O=0.983]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.017,O=0.965]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.010,O=0.986]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.002,O=0.983]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.002,ORG=0.001,O=0.997]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.002,O=0.992]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.017,LOC=0.015,ORG=0.006,O=0.963]	O	O
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.936,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.034,O=0.026]	PER	PER
.	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.994]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
	25-YEAR
-----------
Move choice:
Launch query on token 9 "TRAINER"
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.996,O=0.000]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.988,O=0.003]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.016,O=0.983]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.017,O=0.965]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.010,O=0.986]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.014,ORG=0.002,O=0.983]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.002,ORG=0.001,O=0.997]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.002,O=0.992]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.017,LOC=0.015,ORG=0.006,O=0.963]	O	O
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.936,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.034,O=0.026]	PER	PER
.	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.994]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
	TRAINER
	25-YEAR
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 6 "25-YEAR" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.996,O=0.000]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.988,O=0.003]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.016,O=0.983]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.017,O=0.965]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.009,O=0.987]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.002,ORG=0.000,O=0.998]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.002,ORG=0.001,O=0.997]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.002,O=0.992]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.017,LOC=0.015,ORG=0.006,O=0.963]	O	O
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.936,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.034,O=0.026]	PER	PER
.	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.994]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
	TRAINER
-----------
Move choice:
io.hybridcrowd.gameplay.Game$Wait@5a7
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.996,O=0.000]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.988,O=0.003]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.016,O=0.983]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.017,O=0.965]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.009,O=0.987]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.002,ORG=0.000,O=0.998]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.002,ORG=0.001,O=0.997]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.002,O=0.992]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.017,LOC=0.015,ORG=0.006,O=0.963]	O	O
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.936,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.034,O=0.026]	PER	PER
.	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.994]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
	TRAINER
-----------
Next event:
Got response on token 9 "TRAINER" = O
-----------
TOKEN	DIST	TAG	GUESS
-------------
REUTER	[PER=0.001,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.996,O=0.000]	PER	ORG
HORSE	[PER=0.004,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.988,O=0.003]	O	ORG
RACING	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.001,ORG=0.016,O=0.983]	O	O
-	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.000,O=1.000]	O	O
PIVOTAL	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.016,ORG=0.017,O=0.965]	PER	O
ENDS	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.003,ORG=0.009,O=0.987]	O	O
25-YEAR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.002,ORG=0.000,O=0.998]	O	O
WAIT	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.002,ORG=0.001,O=0.997]	O	O
FOR	[PER=0.000,LOC=0.005,ORG=0.002,O=0.993]	O	O
TRAINER	[PER=0.002,LOC=0.002,ORG=0.001,O=0.994]	O	O
PRESCOTT	[PER=0.936,LOC=0.004,ORG=0.033,O=0.027]	PER	PER
.	[PER=0.005,LOC=0.000,ORG=0.001,O=0.994]	O	O

-----------
Current job postings un-answered: 0
Current available humans: 5
Current in-flight queries: 
-----------
Move choice:
io.hybridcrowd.gameplay.Game$TurnIn@63c
